RT O
@jordancornette O
: O
This O
is O
how O
Alex B-PER
Rodriguez I-PER
spends O
his O
free O
time O
. O
Hangin O
out O
with O
@joelcornette O
at O
Notre B-ORG
Dame I-ORG
tailgates O
. O
ARod B-PER
is O
Irish O
h… O

RT O
@AuthorGiaLee O
: O
I O
' O
ve O
titled O
this O
one O
" O
Interplay O
of O
Light O
&amp O
; O
Shadow O
. O
" O
Took O
it O
in O
beautiful O
Columbia B-LOC
, O
SC B-LOC
. O
http://t.co/7ubozPWFAa O

Jillian B-PER
enjoys O
a O
birthday O
bath--and O
a O
blue O
snout O
. O
Join O
us O
this O
weekend O
: O
http://t.co/Pr5z9pQ8Ea O
Photo O
by O
Sandi B-PER
Wong I-PER
http://t.co/uQWCB32Vy8 O

Looking O
for O
a O
great O
moms O
group O
in O
Peoria B-LOC
? O
Join O
us O
starting O
Sept O
16th O
! O
http://t.co/SuKvqee4ls O
#parenting O
#peoria B-LOC
http://t.co/C5lj7m5kvH O

RT O
@JimBeam O
: O
Egypt B-LOC
has O
pyramids O
, O
we O
have O
rackhouses O
. O
Visit O
the O
Jim B-LOC
Beam I-LOC
American I-LOC
Stillhouse I-LOC
http://t.co/2tvkUNKPJi O
http://t.co/dOro4Misls O

RT O
@WiredUK O
: O
Minecraft B-OTHER
creator O
Notch B-PER
says O
his O
billions O
have O
made O
him O
miserable O
http://t.co/wMnoZp2hLv O
http://t.co/iUogGT6d3N O

Claude B-PER
Richmond I-PER
has O
a O
smart O
way O
to O
fix O
the O
Senate B-ORG
. O
His O
column O
today O
in O
NewsKamloops O
. O
http://t.co/1XpNbERcI5 O
http://t.co/IffI1moyQA O

Such O
tragedy O
of O
a O
young O
17 O
year O
old O
who O
lost O
her O
life O
at O
the O
Sandia B-LOC
Crest I-LOC
in O
#ABQ B-LOC
http://t.co/Qze8ts6pt3 O
http://t.co/FTd8M5JyBL O

RT O
@EarthPics O
_ O
HD O
: O
Silver B-LOC
Falls I-LOC
, O
Oregon B-LOC
http://t.co/RulgE3iCWT O

News O
: O
IPC B-ORG
President O
Sir B-PER
Philip I-PER
Craven I-PER
named O
@SportsBusiness O
Innovator O
of O
the O
Year O
http://t.co/UPbsJYP5Hq O
http://t.co/xPVoeZeUO9 O

RT O
@BEAUTIFULPlCS O
: O
Manarola B-LOC
, O
#Italy B-LOC
. O
Photo O
by O
Lars B-PER
Kehrel I-PER
. O
http://t.co/AXQvIM6bze O

RT O
@WNTonight O
: O
Hillary B-PER
Clinton I-PER
says O
Joe B-PER
Biden I-PER
" O
could O
be O
a O
good O
president O
. O
" O
http://t.co/Ca7tAGvs2s O
http://t.co/YOqobQHwHy O

http://t.co/vfdYRTVuHC O
Living O
Room O
Furniture O
Ottawa B-LOC
http://t.co/kR6OgzG4aD O

RT O
@UberFootbalI O
: O
On O
this O
day O
, O
8 O
years O
ago O
, O
a O
19-year O
old O
Lionel B-PER
Messi I-PER
did O
this O
. O
Wow O
. O
http://t.co/9Pmra3r8G5 O

RT O
@BE O
_ O
MSprague O
: O
What O
the O
Seahawks B-ORG
should O
have O
done O
, O
Tecmo B-OTHER
Super I-OTHER
Bowl I-OTHER
edition O
: O
http://t.co/ocCNsVOfaK O

RT O
@1DUpdatesARG O
_ O
: O
#NEW O
HQ O
Zayn B-PER
outside O
the O
arena O
6/10 O
#2 O
http://t.co/2z0pyc61xD O

RT O
@ianbremmer O
: O
Still O
Looking O
for O
Putin B-PER
http://t.co/yeyNfxGINw O

MACEDONIA B-LOC
- O
A O
migrant O
waits O
to O
reach O
a O
train O
heading O
to O
the O
border O
with O
Serbia B-LOC
in O
Gevgelija B-LOC
. O
By O
@dilkoff O
#AFP O
http://t.co/qIatDV90ph O

RT O
@Bipartisanism O
: O
The O
difference O
between O
resisting O
arrest O
and O
aggravated O
assault O
shown O
by O
Peter B-PER
Griffin I-PER
. O
#McKinney B-LOC
http://t.co/HUkpYbuGGR O

RT O
@FanJam O
: O
Kobe B-PER
to O
Shaq B-PER
: O
The O
most O
infamous O
alley-oop O
ever O
http://t.co/sC7q6I2JaC O

RT O
@WanderlustersUK O
: O
My O
4 O
Wheeled O
Adventure O
Across O
Nepal B-LOC
http://t.co/I4wXjV0ZR8 O
#wluk O
#ttot O
http://t.co/XnhcdtYRoI O

RT O
@voxdotcom O
: O
This O
is O
what O
the O
students O
at O
Ted B-PER
Cruz I-PER
' O
s O
announcement O
were O
saying O
on O
Yik B-OTHER
Yak I-OTHER
http://t.co/Gaz0V2QW79 O
http://t.co/uEkEDda4CG O

@CurbedDetroit O
: O
Grayhaven B-LOC
Island I-LOC
in O
#Detroit B-LOC
has O
2 O
historic O
waterfront O
gems O
on O
the O
market O
: O
http://t.co/bD7KQoeDYi O
http://t.co/OYDxiwF865 O

RT O
@TechCrunch O
: O
Disrupt O
London B-LOC
Startup B-LOC
Alley I-LOC
registration O
is O
open O
http://t.co/AL15H8P4Qz O
http://t.co/7wZq6FjQq2 O

RT O
@NYTArchives O
: O
The O
March O
on O
Washington B-LOC
, O
this O
day O
in O
1963 O
: O
http://t.co/3ieLpaBXBV O
http://t.co/MraydxxRMS O

Turns O
out O
Pretty B-PER
Ricky I-PER
was O
pretty B-PER
icky O
in O
Wellington B-LOC
. O
http://t.co/myYRi2RK2W O
http://t.co/o7yc4G7yFP O

What O
a O
great O
evening O
session O
! O
Ukraine O
finishes O
Day O
5 O
in O
1st O
position O
of O
the O
medals O
table O
, O
Russia B-LOC
in O
2nd O
and O
GB B-LOC
in O
3rd O
http://t.co/VBw9UOZ7oX O

Deans O
from O
GSO B-ORG
colleges O
discuss O
preferred O
site O
for O
collaborative O
University O
campus O
downtown O
@South O
Elm&amp O
; O
Lee B-LOC
streets I-LOC
. O
http://t.co/JowW3An3z4 O

RT O
@EarthPixDaiIy O
: O
Greenland B-LOC
http://t.co/7QDDavkEqU O

RT O
@Politics O
_ O
PR O
: O
Ex-Yahoo O
CEO O
: O
I O
would O
pay O
Jon B-PER
Stewart I-PER
$ O
100 O
million O
per O
year O
to O
relaunch O
his O
show O
: O
http://t.co/0DptqhDrTy O
#p2 O
http://t.co/… O

RT O
@slatest O
: O
As O
backlash O
builds O
, O
Giuliani B-PER
cites O
Obama B-PER
' O
s O
white O
relatives O
as O
evidence O
of O
non-racism O
: O
http://t.co/3SaxM5lO82 O
http://t.co/4bYcV… O

Space B-OTHER
Shuttle I-OTHER
spotted O
over O
the O
Lincoln B-LOC
Memorial I-LOC
at O
10 O
: O
07 O
AM O
#spottheshuttle O
http://t.co/bXal7HN7 O

RT O
@KennettDems O
: O
RT O
if O
you O
are O
voting O
for O
Democrats B-ORG
on O
November O
4th O
! O
#GOTV B-OTHER
http://t.co/RV0DypwPaT O

What O
do O
health O
heroes O
look O
like O
? O
Dr B-PER
Lucille I-PER
Corti I-PER
died O
AIDS B-OTHER
1996 O
, O
Dr B-PER
Lukwiya I-PER
died O
Ebola B-OTHER
2000 O
. O
52yrs O
serving O
#Uganda B-LOC
http://t.co/dYrza1lGYT O

Today O
21 O
years O
ago O
in O
Australia B-LOC
was O
born O
one O
of O
the O
people O
who O
ilunima O
me O
with O
his O
smile O
#HappyBirthdayAshton O
http://t.co/KMYdrnsZDL O

RT O
@ltsChuckBass O
: O
sushi O
with O
Ed B-PER
= O
dream O
date O
http://t.co/PnYra294tE O

RT O
@Entrepreneur O
: O
Happy O
Birthday O
, O
Steve B-PER
Jobs I-PER
. O
http://t.co/2VshrXOiJ2 O

RT O
@ThislsAmazing O
: O
Johnny B-PER
Depp I-PER
, O
1989 O
http://t.co/1xSHDkYTuF O

RT O
@idontcurve O
: O
Rihanna B-PER
looking O
as O
thick O
as O
ever O
http://t.co/VYWloMhDId O

RT O
@beautifulpixx O
: O
Seoraksan B-LOC
National I-LOC
Park I-LOC
in O
South B-LOC
Korea I-LOC
. O
http://t.co/xWbmImGNNY O

@PierceTheFresno O
#Darah B-PER
Dan I-PER
and O
Sarah B-PER
: O
D O
http://t.co/JeQtd3clmX O

Nana B-PER
meets O
Conchita B-PER
at O
Paris B-LOC
( O
exhibition O
Jean B-PER
Paul I-PER
Gaultier I-PER
) O
http://t.co/4rJQPa2Um8 O

#Bears B-ORG
coach O
John B-PER
Fox I-PER
meets O
the O
Dolphins B-ORG
after O
his O
first O
game O
, O
a O
preseason O
win O
: O
http://t.co/MDtDMa3Ahy O
http://t.co/fSZ6rigQrE O

Are O
you O
ready O
for O
some O
football O
? O
VARSITY B-OTHER
ZONE I-OTHER
is O
back O
tonight O
with O
the O
best O
coverage O
of O
AZ B-LOC
high O
school O
football O
! O
http://t.co/ruZMgKQ77n O

Apple B-ORG
Passes O
Nikon B-ORG
to O
Become O
2nd O
Most O
Popular O
Camera O
Brand O
on O
Flickr B-OTHER
http://t.co/psG70DGdKQ. O
@Canon O
#mareketshare O
http://t.co/knmqfvpe9c O

Throwback O
Thursday O
of O
me O
, O
aged O
4 O
, O
taking O
a O
ride O
with O
my O
best O
mate O
/ O
very O
docile O
pet O
sheep O
Kate B-PER
. O
#love O
#tbt O
http://t.co/PE1Oxrxrdt O

RT O
@Steve O
_ O
OS O
: O
DeAndre B-PER
Jordan I-PER
Achievement O
Unlocked O
http://t.co/GDwbtl6BgA O

RT O
@SMendesTour O
: O
Shawn B-PER
with O
Ohio B-LOC
squad O
today O
at O
his O
M&amp O
; O
G O
in O
Cleveland B-LOC
, O
OH B-LOC
. O
( O
7/21-2015 O
) O
. O
@ayhtdwshawn O
http://t.co/9umdEukah7 O

RT O
@CHANEL O
: O
Alice B-PER
Dellal I-PER
, O
Kristen B-PER
Stewart I-PER
, O
and O
Vanessa B-PER
Paradis I-PER
, O
faces O
of O
the O
new O
handbag O
campaign O
http://t.co/CBpZygJZzt O

#ISIS B-ORG
be O
like O
, O
http://t.co/y5FWxXO6x1 O

RT O
@Glamberttt O
_ O
: O
I O
think O
that O
Adam B-PER
and O
Sauli B-PER
are O
having O
fun O
right O
now O
at O
their O
bedroom O
, O
a O
lot O
of O
fun O
. O
. O
. O
Morning O
sex O
; O
D O
. O
. O
. O
http://t.co/js O
... O

RT O
@historyofsound O
: O
John B-PER
Lennon I-PER
creating O
. O
http://t.co/gy48kIDunz O

RT O
@crooksandliars O
: O
Wingnut O
Larry B-PER
Klayman I-PER
Slaps O
Hillary B-PER
Clinton I-PER
With O
Racketeering O
Lawsuit O
http://t.co/XvUwHesD8i O
http://t.co/98iAUf2xRj O

RT O
@mjesusgz O
: O
Morning O
Venice B-LOC
by O
Angela B-PER
Hofman I-PER
http://t.co/AoUUoHxiGB O

The O
public O
process O
for O
IndyCar B-OTHER
#Boston B-LOC
is O
underway O
. O
http://t.co/OxQ2SBPVrM O
http://t.co/epuXFJaKqv O

RT O
@sranysovok O
: O
- O
Blatter B-PER
, O
we O
happy O
? O
- O
Yeah O
, O
we O
happy O
http://t.co/T3fUPiCa3R O

Good O
morning O
, O
Switzerland B-LOC
. O
You O
' O
re O
looking O
very O
quaint O
http://t.co/IHAxSQU1w9 O

RT O
@Erwinlandman72 O
: O
De O
auto O
van O
Max B-PER
Verstappen I-PER
van O
hyacinten O
bloemenvgemaakt#bloemendagen#AnnaPaulowna O
http://t.co/gyFeXrVFNy O

Chicago B-LOC
kind O
of O
night O
in O
Austin B-LOC
last O
night O
! O
Greatest O
live O
band O
on O
earth O
. O
#PJACL2014 O
http://t.co/g7eRPTSAFD O

RT O
@businessinsider O
: O
22 O
stunning O
aerial O
photos O
of O
Cuba B-LOC
http://t.co/hfBkNqh9Pm O
http://t.co/e6Vbw3UJWX O

RT O
@ngadc O
: O
#HappyBirthday O
Gustav B-PER
Klimt I-PER
, O
Austrian O
painter O
born O
#OnThisDay O
in O
1862 O
. O
" O
Baby O
( O
Cradle B-PER
) O
" O
1917/1918 O
http://t.co/ULTJQ2RQJ1 O

RT O
@mashable O
: O
Well O
, O
this O
bathroom O
at O
a O
Sochi B-LOC
Olympic O
venue O
is O
rather O
awkward O
: O
http://t.co/VHgtsftlYp O
http://t.co/OT184d8AiH O

Picture O
of O
the O
woman O
behind O
the O
original O
voice O
of O
Siri B-OTHER
. O
Susan B-PER
Bennett I-PER
: O
http://t.co/FdIxloNVLi O

RT O
@CuntsWatching O
: O
What O
a O
scoop O
for O
the O
Daily B-ORG
Mail I-ORG
. O
Incredible O
exclusive O
story O
. O
http://t.co/0OOQ8jPbyA O

Hastings B-ORG
6 O
Hudson B-ORG
2 O
W O
#statetourney#10aaa O
http://t.co/U7mfOmBhaL O

@georgelopez O
when O
u O
coming O
to O
#Texas B-LOC
? O
When O
u O
do O
be O
safe O
http://t.co/7iON87PJd6 O

Hello O
from O
VEGAS B-LOC
. O
Oh O
yeah O
. O
And O
the O
Grand B-LOC
Canyon I-LOC
. O
http://t.co/dXFind87 O

. O
@Adidas O
&amp O
; O
@Nike O
compete O
in O
race O
to O
build O
factories O
in O
the O
US B-LOC
http://t.co/XiM3CPl2XZ O
#MadeinUSA O
http://t.co/k0OUckdFGk O

RT O
@radiogeyser O
: O
at O
the O
Christmas B-OTHER
Market I-OTHER
in O
Munich B-LOC
, O
Germany B-LOC
today O
. O
. O
. O
http://t.co/dYBRA4xYSs O

Photo O
essay O
: O
28 O
things O
not O
to O
miss O
in O
Kenya B-LOC
http://t.co/xPWQk7fRnr O
via O
@manoukbob O
#ttot O
#photograhy O
#travel O
http://t.co/xWJH9YwrmH O

Celebrando B-OTHER
independencia O
de O
Chile B-LOC
con O
@cristobalcobo O
y O
amigos O
y O
familia O
en O
Lima B-LOC
http://t.co/M5mOeOdZzY O

RT O
@Adweek O
: O
Sean B-PER
Astin I-PER
returns O
as O
Rudy B-OTHER
for O
excellent O
@ESPN O
college O
football O
promo O
: O
http://t.co/AVziQwn3EH O
http://t.co/fMq99M3JyL O

RT O
@MannfredNikolai O
: O
Russia B-LOC
Using O
INTERPOL B-ORG
To O
Target O
Russian O
Dissidents O
Living O
Abroad O
http://t.co/RcEzN9RgOk O
http://t.co/URcUBeRB5G O

Massive O
crowd O
in O
Hapahuwa B-LOC
, O
#Kurunegala O
District O
, O
awaiting O
the O
arrival O
of O
President B-PER
Rajapaksa I-PER
. O
#SriLanka O
http://t.co/29SUqjRLne O

RT O
@JMakamba O
: O
At O
Huduma B-LOC
Center I-LOC
in O
Machakos B-LOC
Post O
Office O
in O
Kenya B-LOC
- O
one-stop O
for O
33 O
govt O
services O
. O
We O
want O
to O
do O
this O
in O
Tanzania B-LOC
. O
http://t.c… O

How O
the O
Blackhawks B-ORG
get O
to O
your O
TV O
. O
I O
didn O
' O
t O
break O
anything O
http://t.co/5jL59WslVF O

RT O
@cencio4 O
: O
U O
. O
S O
. O
may O
deploy O
F-22 B-LOC
Raptor O
stealth O
jets O
to O
Europe B-LOC
to O
counter O
" O
Russian O
threat O
" O
http://t.co/2cSKaeHSee O
http://t.co/av4cO2R4la O

Harlem B-LOC
in O
the O
snow O
http://t.co/XXZJgarlA6 O

RT O
@UToledoMedia O
: O
The O
@ToledoRockets O
take O
on O
Navy B-ORG
at O
noon O
Saturday O
in O
the O
Glass B-LOC
Bowl I-LOC
#GoRockets O
#RocketNation O
http://t.co/IDIXOK0DnK O

RT O
@JakeBoys O
: O
Me O
and O
Niall B-PER
Horan I-PER
are O
best O
friends O
http://t.co/bjaN2UQMCO O

RT O
@lonelyplanetUSA O
: O
3 O
easy O
, O
family-friendly O
road O
trips O
in O
the O
USA B-LOC
http://t.co/KWsUZwM0iK O
#lproadtrip O
http://t.co/MdeQ0PXXdB O

MEXICO B-LOC
- O
Alleged O
end O
of O
tunnel O
through O
which O
drug O
lord O
El B-PER
Chapo I-PER
could O
have O
escaped O
from O
prison O
. O
By O
@YuriYurisky O
#AFP B-OTHER
http://t.co/PNOWhWS4qb O

RT O
@ebubekiryaman O
: O
Kyoto B-LOC
- O
Japan B-LOC
http://t.co/7ShkXJwg9x O

RT O
@not O
_ O
romo O
: O
RETWEET O
to O
annoy O
a O
Seahawks B-ORG
fan O
. O
http://t.co/Hu54q6pMtr O

San B-LOC
Marcos I-LOC
, O
the O
land O
of O
the O
enchanting O
river O
. O
http://t.co/o4tJGosIWS O

RT O
@SportsCenter O
: O
Intense O
. O
. O
. O
Ronda B-PER
Rousey I-PER
and O
Bethe B-PER
Correia I-PER
are O
ready O
for O
UFC B-OTHER
190 O
. O
http://t.co/RMEGqGMrtQ O

RT O
@Breaking911 O
: O
CNN B-ORG
: O
ISIS B-ORG
Luring O
American O
Women O
With O
Nutella B-OTHER
, O
Kittens B-OTHER
&amp O
; O
Emojis B-OTHER
- O
http://t.co/qckMS7LKDs O
http://t.co/1Ss6wFtScA O

RT O
@HistoricalPics O
: O
The O
famous O
Folsom B-OTHER
Prison I-OTHER
performance O
by O
Johnny B-PER
Cash I-PER
. O
1968 O
. O
http://t.co/xGnCFZyDlY O

Stuart B-PER
Wheeler I-PER
tells O
@MichaelLCrick O
that O
@DouglasCarswell O
is O
" O
obvious O
" O
person O
to O
succeed O
Nigel B-PER
Farage I-PER
http://t.co/vAqK17H212 O

RT O
@SoSoGay O
: O
UKIP B-ORG
at O
Pride O
in O
London B-LOC
: O
An O
open O
letter O
http://t.co/jjMbAdIJiI O
http://t.co/CGfpy5viFF O

RT O
@LucyWilliamson O
: O
Flowers O
and O
messages O
outside O
Danwon B-ORG
high I-ORG
school I-ORG
in O
Ansan B-LOC
#sewol O
http://t.co/DJUKMOppmt O

RT O
@TheAtlantic O
: O
Wall B-LOC
Street I-LOC
' O
s O
role O
in O
the O
Greek B-LOC
debt O
crisis O
http://t.co/Q77NASAWmR O
http://t.co/uOQ7ngFry6 O

RT O
@politico O
: O
Report O
: O
Saudi B-LOC
ex-foreign O
minister O
Prince B-PER
Saud I-PER
al-Faisal I-PER
dies O
http://t.co/WTPkDqq2T1 O
| O
AP O
Photo O
http://t.co/90dI596EPp O

RT O
@SoloNoticias1D O
: O
Harry B-PER
en O
el O
show O
de O
Argentina B-LOC
, O
hace O
instantes O
: O
D O
#Noticias1D O
#OneDirection O
#1DenArgentina O
http://t.co/bA8io5dSXc O

For O
the O
post O
yoga O
pants O
generation O
Minecraft B-OTHER
is O
more O
important O
than O
Facebook B-ORG
#Minecraft B-OTHER
#creeper O
http://t.co/HjGKGycg1S O

RT O
@CNBCnow O
: O
BREAKING O
: O
Verizon B-ORG
to O
buy O
AOL B-ORG
for O
$ O
4 O
. O
4 O
billion O
http://t.co/B5oH6OuyGs O
http://t.co/zsSrb8yqvp O

The O
#BundleOfJoy O
baby O
is O
cute O
, O
but O
Eddie B-PER
and O
Debbie B-PER
sure O
had O
cute O
ones O
of O
their O
own O
. O
Carrie B-PER
&amp O
; O
Todd B-PER
. O
#tcmparty O
http://t.co/28mqdaxEp6 O

RT O
@EricHolthaus O
: O
NASA B-ORG
issues O
an O
ominous O
warning O
for O
a O
vulnerable O
ice O
shelf O
in O
Antarctica B-LOC
: O
http://t.co/fAPE9tlP47 O
http://t.co/WdXGVQUDRn O

More O
needed O
, O
preferably O
ones O
grown O
in O
England B-LOC
#nativetoaisia O
http://t.co/pRPP3Lp46C O

Mickey O
' O
s O
Diner I-OTHER
in O
a O
train O
car O
, O
where O
I O
' O
ve O
learned O
Mighty B-OTHER
Ducks I-OTHER
filmed O
. O
Reports O
say O
Emilio B-PER
Estevez I-PER
was O
nice O
#stpaul O
http://t.co/7n15ZNQAYJ O

RT O
@WSJ O
: O
As O
#Sochi2014 O
gets O
underway O
, O
Google B-ORG
rolls O
out O
a O
pro-gay O
rights O
" O
doodle O
. O
" O
http://t.co/mwIm0YXY6m O
http://t.co/Y8iFFJWS8S O

Belated O
tweet O
, O
but O
meant O
to O
say O
I O
loved O
the B-OTHER
powerful O
way O
Flora B-PER
Robson I-PER
strutted O
around O
in O
THE B-OTHER
SEA I-OTHER
HAWK I-OTHER
. O
#tcmff O
http://t.co/maAeiS4iZp O

Farmers O
from O
Prespa B-LOC
&amp O
; O
Namangan B-LOC
find O
common O
ground O
in O
#innovations O
for O
#sustainableagriculture O
: O
http://t.co/pRHDE6B0hU O
http://t.co/p4uNxHpzMd O

Arrived O
Minkaman B-LOC
- O
where O
victims O
of I-OTHER
mass O
murder O
fled O
on O
West B-OTHER
Bank I-OTHER
of I-OTHER
Nile I-OTHER
#SouthSudan B-LOC
- O
protection O
@PeaceForce O
http://t.co/EPok9875mn O

RT O
@MexicoEsMagico O
: O
Maguey B-ORG
Agave I-ORG
Azul I-ORG
en I-ORG
Tequila I-ORG
, O
Jalisco B-LOC
. O
| O
http://t.co/DRvYqAteZ0 O

As O
the O
' O
L O
' O
train O
passes O
over O
the O
Wells B-LOC
Street I-LOC
bridge O
, O
a O
sunny O
morning O
in O
Chicago B-LOC
http://t.co/0qBIALqzau O

RT O
@CBSSports O
: O
Possible O
Duncan B-PER
pep O
talk O
? O
http://t.co/UErZX0PG9U O

RT O
@Planet O
_ O
EXO O
: O
[ O
Preview O
] O
150619 O
ICN B-LOC
to O
BKK- O
Sehun B-PER
( O
cr O
IB O
) O
http://t.co/gpuqMr3iwC O

RT O
@EnglishRussia1 O
: O
Boris B-PER
Yeltsin I-PER
dressed O
as O
shaman O
while O
visiting O
Siberian B-LOC
shamans O
of O
Tuva B-PER
Republic I-PER
http://t.co/DdHmRLkF3Y O

RT O
@T O
_ O
_ O
twitt O
: O
Edie B-PER
Baskin I-PER
in O
Yves B-ORG
Saint I-ORG
Laurent I-ORG
Ensemble I-ORG
, O
photo O
by O
Berry B-PER
Berenson I-PER
for O
Vogue B-ORG
, O
1972 O
http://t.co/uQwABBmm4o O

RT O
@MarthaStewart O
: O
My O
birthday O
rainbow O
over O
my O
Skylands O
home O
in O
Maine B-LOC
. O
I O
hope O
it O
was O
a O
sign O
of O
everything O
good O
http://t.co/7L2Tjjs2EM O

Honored O
to O
be O
here O
in O
LA B-LOC
@jworldwatch O
IWitness O
Award O
given O
to O
Intel B-OTHER
4 I-OTHER
commitment O
to O
only O
use O
conflict O
free O
minerals O
http://t.co/SVdT6e6lcw O

RT O
@CBSSports O
: O
David B-PER
Blatt I-PER
has O
a O
new O
gameplan O
that O
can O
' O
t O
miss O
. O
. O
. O
http://t.co/2Gs2Prgoil O

RT O
@thehill O
: O
Warren B-PER
pokes O
fun O
at O
Scott B-PER
Brown I-PER
, O
Sarah B-PER
Palin I-PER
: O
http://t.co/Zo8C9xJgC1 O
http://t.co/VJj8tzgBLD O

Harrods B-LOC
Hotel I-LOC
Kuala I-LOC
Lumpur I-LOC
, O
a O
7-star O
hotel I-LOC
to O
open O
in O
2018 O
- O
http://t.co/Urtj3Lf8Zv O
#MyFest2015 O
#Malaysia B-LOC
#Harrods B-LOC
http://t.co/leKL0UdnZc O

RT O
@nbafinestnews O
: O
Best O
Small O
Foward O
•Final O
Four• O
RT O
for O
Paul B-PER
George I-PER
FAV O
for O
Anthony B-PER
Davis I-PER
http://t.co/LwX7aOpezr O

Brent B-PER
Seabrook I-PER
celebrates O
his O
goal O
, O
but O
the O
good O
times O
didn O
' O
t O
last O
. O
#Blackhawks B-ORG
fall O
: O
http://t.co/15beLFobb4 O
http://t.co/snuRjMDY2S O

Luna O
3/4 O
hahaha O
#EclipseLunar O
#LunaDeSangre O
#BloodMoon O
en O
#Mexico B-LOC
http://t.co/qiUiJhfYd2 O

Good O
times O
at O
JFK B-LOC
#CNYJFK O
RT O
@KristySmorol O
: O
Look O
who O
I O
ran O
into O
on O
my O
early O
morning O
flight O
to O
NYC B-LOC
. O
@BrandonRothCNY O
http://t.co/ZWRChjVzHd" O

RT O
@BBCWorld O
: O
What O
the O
19th O
century O
Welsh B-LOC
settlers O
in O
Patagonia B-LOC
teach O
us O
about O
migration O
http://t.co/S5AhcAA7mn O
http://t.co/m1bMkuPPjN O

Tuesday O
in O
a O
pigsty O
. O
Joliet B-LOC
, O
Illinois B-LOC
http://t.co/wWhRqiP7Ik O

RT O
@SportsCenter O
: O
#3 O
FSU B-ORG
goes O
down O
! O
NC B-ORG
State I-ORG
UPSETS O
Florida B-ORG
State I-ORG
17-16 O
. O
#FSUvsNCSU O
http://t.co/WBfwdL7L O

RT O
@DougatNokia O
: O
Hmmm O
. O
#Nokia B-ORG
vs O
Samsung B-ORG
developer O
sessions O
. O
1 O
hour O
after O
start O
. O
#NokiaMWC O
#NokiaDev O
http://t.co/wV8vxTJ935" O

RT O
@tkylemac O
: O
" O
Andy B-PER
Cohen I-PER
is O
now O
following O
you O
on O
Twitter B-ORG
" O
http://t.co/en1uelCkxi O

RT O
@LibertyLynx O
: O
Adidas B-ORG
to O
close O
200 O
shops O
in O
Russia B-LOC
March O
05 O
- O
CNNMoney B-OTHER
http://t.co/PfwnmOR9xH O
Oh O
no! O
http://t.co/vVr8ZAg47O O

RT O
@TheNBACentral O
: O
Charles B-PER
Barkely I-PER
on O
Kobe B-PER
Bryant I-PER
: O
" O
Old O
people O
don O
' O
t O
get O
healthy O
, O
they O
die O
. O
" O
http://t.co/garIVTG6LZ O

RT O
@ O
_ O
globalhealth O
: O
David B-PER
Evans I-PER
from O
WHO B-ORG
on O
global B-OTHER
health I-OTHER
2035 I-OTHER
report O
key O
messages O
http://t.co/zyKokCG678 O

RT O
@historic O
_ O
racing O
: O
James B-PER
Dean I-PER
and O
his O
beautiful O
Porsche B-OTHER
550 I-OTHER
Spyder I-OTHER
. O
( O
his O
cursed O
car O
) O
http://t.co/wPapEnQFHN O

RT O
@Cubs O
: O
#Cubs B-ORG
win O
! O
Final O
: O
Cubs O
2 O
, O
#Dodgers B-ORG
0 O
( O
plus O
a O
Jake B-PER
Arrieta I-PER
no-hitter O
) O
. O
#LetsGo O
http://t.co/K0ojeS4gjb O

Things O
are O
looking O
up O
from O
the O
crown O
of O
the O
Tribune B-LOC
Tower I-LOC
http://t.co/tMpYjJ4LJy O

Just O
a O
heads O
up O
some O
light O
showers O
are O
being O
reported O
across O
the O
Lower B-LOC
Hudson I-LOC
, O
NNJ B-LOC
, O
LI B-LOC
, O
and O
S O
. O
CT O
. O
@PIX11News O
http://t.co/tCLNUlP7fz O

RT O
@ThislsAmazing O
: O
60s O
London B-LOC
girls O
protesting O
for O
mini O
skirts O
http://t.co/ewe7DVYmaC O

RT O
@businessinsider O
: O
Online O
shopping O
has O
arrived O
in O
North B-LOC
Korea I-LOC
http://t.co/xMSwaJQSbR O
http://t.co/LrS8Ms9wEw O

Glass B-OTHER
Cliff I-OTHER
Walk I-OTHER
at O
Yunyang B-LOC
Longgang I-LOC
, O
#Chongqing B-LOC
- O
http://t.co/hNaiNT5yW8 O
#China B-LOC
#outdoors O
#ttot O
#amazing O
http://t.co/pJ2GW7ZR8t O

Report O
finds O
Pak B-PER
&amp O
; O
Sri B-LOC
Lanka I-LOC
way O
more O
generous O
than O
India B-LOC
. O
http://t.co/xAkFJLwLZ5 O
http://t.co/s7YMD5Oygm O
yes O
we O
are O
a O
selfish O
bunch O

RT O
@PJPartington O
: O
Canadian O
and O
US B-LOC
GHG B-OTHER
emissions O
relative O
to O
various O
base O
years O
#cdnpoli O
http://t.co/RSJitSzTAe O

RT O
@RollingStone O
: O
Watch O
Eddie B-PER
Vedder I-PER
perform O
" O
Better B-OTHER
Man I-OTHER
" O
on O
#LateShow O
: O
http://t.co/1mr2N2nYWy O
http://t.co/jfs1EXDHLY O

RT O
@mjesusgz O
: O
Garden O
in O
Cleveland O
, O
Ohio B-LOC
http://t.co/Ki3vgqbiRj O

Onlookers O
all O
the O
way O
to O
platform O
across O
the O
street O
on O
Shanghai B-LOC
st O
. O
#OccupyHK O
http://t.co/PniLyaEbsE O

#Iran B-LOC
central O
bank O
governor O
describes O
post-sanction O
challenges O
in O
rare O
itvw O
http://t.co/QfJmA9gk8g O
@FT O
via O
@borzou O
http://t.co/K5EQ6lKwH8 O

Hushed O
conversations O
continue O
before O
House B-ORG
unveils O
changes O
to O
#heroin B-OTHER
bill O
. O
#kyga15 O
http://t.co/oEdS76ou8t O

RT O
@GlazerBooHooHoo O
: O
Sometimes O
I O
scroll O
through O
Twitter B-OTHER
and O
it O
sounds O
like O
this O
http://t.co/B5pJ0XWmjb O

New O
#Bulls B-ORG
center O
Pau B-PER
Gasol I-PER
meets O
the O
Spanish O
press O
. O
He O
' O
s O
tall O
http://t.co/jzgeTBq14l O

RT O
@ianbremmer O
: O
Beijing B-LOC
http://t.co/aipOJaOXLT O

RT O
@tekubitu O
: O
From O
Alberto B-PER
Saldivar I-PER
on O
Facebook B-ORG
http://t.co/GpF6XMGrun O

RT O
@herrharr O
: O
A O
wildling O
and O
a O
viking O
. O
Game B-OTHER
of I-OTHER
Thrones I-OTHER
vs O
Vikings B-OTHER
in O
Budapest B-LOC
. O
http://t.co/BZWjjOMMTu O

Tonight O
in O
Syracuse B-LOC
! O
Photo O
Show O
reception O
- O
hope O
to O
see O
you O
there O
! O
#syracuse B-LOC
#photography O
#photoshow O
http://t.co/G7RTveQ9jx O

Could O
the O
#Preds B-ORG
draft I-OTHER
one O
of O
these O
wingers O
next O
week O
at O
the O
2015 O
NHL B-OTHER
Draft I-OTHER
? O
--&gt O
; O
http://t.co/dbt2YwyRip O
http://t.co/oIntnVdLUO O

Truman B-PER
likes O
to O
be O
the O
center O
of O
attention O
. O
http://t.co/zZHVBZyAr4 O

Watch O
Canada B-ORG
v O
Czech B-ORG
Republic I-ORG
LIVE O
in O
30 O
mins O
on O
http://t.co/2Xrey6ha5U O
http://t.co/MKly7pro6V O

RT O
@TheOnion O
: O
CIA B-ORG
Admits O
Role O
In O
1985 O
Coup O
To O
Oust O
David B-PER
Lee I-PER
Roth I-PER
http://t.co/ToS3s9dzc3 O
http://t.co/Zo9Bqsfs6s O

RT O
@BBCSporf O
: O
Adnan B-PER
Januzaj I-PER
at O
Man B-ORG
United I-ORG
: O
Goals O
: O
4 O
Bookings O
for O
diving O
: O
5 O
http://t.co/HkQcUBIlUc O

Defenseman O
Anthony B-PER
Bitetto I-PER
( O
@ABitetto7 O
) O
has O
inked O
a O
1-year O
deal O
to O
remain O
with O
the O
#Preds B-ORG
--&gt O
; O
http://t.co/9Fs7RhiUUF O
http://t.co/W19tvmZx8q O

RT O
@Recode O
: O
Hewlett-Packard B-ORG
formally O
files O
plan O
to O
split O
up O
http://t.co/b9MAJI5mhU O
by O
@ahess247 O
http://t.co/d6CEzHwmGz O

RT O
@designmilk O
: O
A O
Modern O
, O
Black O
&amp O
; O
White O
Apartment O
in O
Poland B-LOC
http://t.co/1Pa609oXAF O
http://t.co/L3noDpE8nb O

RT O
@LanaDReyCrew O
: O
Lana B-PER
Del I-PER
Rey I-PER
for O
FASHION B-OTHER
magazine O
http://t.co/KDP9rHjQxE O

RT O
@FreeArturo2 O
: O
Stand O
w/@action4IFAW O
Tell O
Zimbabwe B-LOC
Exporting O
Wild O
#elephants🐘 O
is O
WRONG O
✏ O
http://t.co/n9fNs1OEI2 O
#SaveAfricanAnimals O
http… O

RT O
@BuzzFeeders O
: O
17 O
Reasons O
Evan B-PER
Peters I-PER
Dominates O
Your O
Darkest O
Fantasies O
http://t.co/VuDCh96kb9 O
http://t.co/lZOF0tSBgA O

Entertainment B-LOC
City I-LOC
at O
Doha B-LOC
Exhibition I-LOC
Centre I-LOC
is O
open O
till O
11pm O
tonight O
. O
http://t.co/4CDnIZ7RD9 O
#QSF2015 O
PC: O
Kammutty O
http://t.co/6yx82KEPhO O

RT O
@EarthPicturz O
: O
Lonely O
boat O
house O
on O
an O
alpine O
lake O
in O
#Germany B-LOC
. O
Photo O
by O
Mark B-PER
Whale I-PER
. O
http://t.co/e4b7CUe2QT O

RT O
@CNNMoney O
: O
Quentin B-PER
Tarantino I-PER
has O
filed O
a O
suit O
against O
Gawker B-OTHER
. O
http://t.co/PwO6jRsjer O
via O
@gregorywallace O
http://t.co/4Dwk8DC7eR O

RT O
@BreakingBad O
_ O
AMC O
: O
Try O
to O
go O
to O
Mexico B-LOC
and O
you O
may O
just O
end O
up O
in O
Belize B-LOC
. O
#BreakingBad O
http://t.co/0IP33VEhQu O

RT O
@ProyectoAyudaJB O
: O
Mil B-PER
retweets O
en O
20 O
minutos O
? O
BeliebersVoteForJustin O
#MTVHottest O
Justin B-PER
Bieber I-PER
http://t.co/g7KjuT2nw8 O

RT O
@ATHNICO O
: O
Friends O
Bon B-PER
appetite O
. O
. O
. O
Greetings O
from O
Greece B-LOC
👋 O
http://t.co/LGHhkXVcXS O

RT O
@BillGates O
: O
Why O
poor O
countries O
deserve O
cheap O
, O
reliable O
energy O
: O
Midtown B-LOC
Manhattan I-LOC
uses O
more O
than O
all O
of O
Kenya B-LOC
. O
http://t.co/VpWIuZmDjJ O

RT O
@flightradar24 O
: O
Still O
no O
air O
traffic O
above O
10 O
, O
000 O
feet O
in O
Chicago B-LOC
ATC B-LOC
. O
240 O
+ O
flights O
canceled O
to/from O
O O
' O
Hare O
&amp O
; O
Midway B-LOC
airports I-LOC
. O
http://t.… O

RT O
@oxfamgb O
: O
RT O
if O
, O
like O
us O
, O
you O
believe O
in O
these O
3 O
steps O
to O
lasting O
peace O
in O
Gaza B-LOC
. O
#ceasefirenow O
@foreignoffice O
http://t.co/LDPKqrY0uB O

RT O
@Cmdr O
_ O
Hadfield O
: O
Clear O
skies O
at O
last O
, O
from O
Cardiff B-LOC
to O
Belfast B-LOC
to O
Edinburgh B-LOC
to O
London B-LOC
, O
to O
the O
northern O
lights O
, O
and O
beyond O
. O
http://t.co/ O
... O

Announcing O
@VMware O
vCloud O
Air B-ORG
Object I-ORG
Storage I-ORG
, O
powered O
by O
EMC B-ORG
ViPR O
. O
Beta O
coming O
soon O
! O
#VMworld O
http://t.co/KWHJynfEOV O

RT O
@mchungphoto O
: O
A O
car O
drives O
into O
the O
side O
of O
Ajalon B-LOC
Church I-LOC
in O
the O
parking O
lot O
in O
Palm B-LOC
Springs I-LOC
. O
@MyDesert O
http://t.co/ta2p4Tqi12 O

Bruce B-PER
Rauner I-PER
adds O
Edgar B-PER
, O
Bill B-PER
Daley I-PER
, O
Meeks B-PER
to O
transition O
team O
. O
Any O
questions O
? O
http://t.co/XZgObIX2Wk O
http://t.co/Ugd8h8v2Ve O

RT O
@StephGhost O
: O
http://t.co/K9PL3JZjiF O
RT O
@CourtneeHendrix: O
Damn O
Westbrook B-PER
really O
is O
Kobe B-PER
reincarnated. O
Thunder B-ORG
2-7 O
when O
he O
score O
38 O
or O
more O

RT O
@Refugees O
: O
Today O
, O
18-year-old O
Yehya B-PER
became O
the O
1 O
millionth O
Syrian O
to O
register O
as O
a O
refugee O
in O
Lebanon B-LOC
http://t.co/H0SMv4mJbL O

RT O
@dvmonique O
: O
people O
: O
Rihanna B-PER
is O
ugly O
me O
: O
. O
. O
. O
http://t.co/7hW4swtzQN O

Good O
Morning O
Twitter B-ORG
. O
Shall O
We O
Begin O
? O
Lets O
do O
it O
. O
Come O
on O
, O
Toby B-PER
. O
You O
can O
do O
it O
. O
Break O
time O
. O
Pleasant O
Day O
, O
Twitter B-ORG
! O
http://t.co/is3LNWER6J O

RT O
@HistoryInPics O
: O
Twiggy B-PER
in O
a O
paper O
dress O
in O
London B-LOC
, O
1967 O
http://t.co/kNWKgMmGON O

RT O
@Forbes O
: O
Jan B-PER
Koum I-PER
signed O
$ O
19B O
sale O
of O
WhatsApp B-OTHER
to O
FB B-ORG
on O
the O
door O
of O
his O
old O
welfare O
office O
http://t.co/HT3VApXiOB O
http://t.co/UOlLxyFivV O

Come O
visit O
Little B-OTHER
Romo I-OTHER
! O
She O
cuter O
than O
ever O
and O
even O
more O
mischievous O
. O
Photo O
by O
Marianne B-PER
Hale I-PER
#SFGiants O
http://t.co/6RL7aubI4j O

LGA B-LOC
in O
Skopje B-LOC
http://t.co/g57M4aIDJA O

RT O
@KelenKeller38 O
: O
You O
can O
buy O
this O
newborn O
on O
iTunes B-OTHER
http://t.co/Xy3BIbuwSj O

RT O
@SkyFootball O
: O
Andre B-PER
Ayew I-PER
is O
making O
quite O
an O
impression O
on O
the O
Premier B-OTHER
League I-OTHER
with O
#Swans B-OTHER
! O
http://t.co/1sLW0QsCM1 O
http://t.co/SOyvRB5VLR O

Thanks O
to O
all O
who O
visited O
the O
Optimum O
stand O
at O
CIPS B-OTHER
Middle I-OTHER
East I-OTHER
Conference I-OTHER
in O
Abu B-LOC
Dhabi I-LOC
today O
http://t.co/cjaWgWbO3o O
http://t.co/5jBlGGKhYP O

#Chilliwack B-LOC
corn O
maze O
. O
. O
! O
40 O
years O
UFV B-ORG
. O
. O
#aerial O
photo O
by O
Ellen B-PER
Atkin I-PER
http://t.co/14U2nmvdia O

RT O
@SuicideGirls O
: O
Zad B-PER
Suicide I-PER
is O
a O
photographer O
from O
Brazil B-LOC
! O
Learn O
more O
about O
this O
babe O
at O
http://t.co/wy45DcJkq0 O
http://t.co/IuER4P66dc O

Suzy B-PER
on O
the O
streets O
of O
New B-LOC
York I-LOC
#SuzyMenkes O
http://t.co/Ps5dltxDnn O

Great O
job O
last O
night O
Kenny B-PER
. O
Hope O
the O
event O
pushes O
Funny B-OTHER
Gloves I-OTHER
to O
the O
next O
level O
@blackenterprise O
#madeinevanston O
http://t.co/nbjdOqgFin O

RT O
@ManUnitedWorld O
: O
New O
Manchester B-ORG
United I-ORG
shirt O
with O
classic O
sponsorship O
logos O
. O
#MUFC B-ORG
http://t.co/QrbbzOWlSA O

Fantastic O
meeting O
with O
@rmnetwork O
folks O
in O
South B-LOC
Carolina I-LOC
- O
opened O
with O
this O
prayer O
. O
. O
#FaithfullyLGBT O
http://t.co/HFS8qlYw6H O

RT O
@chicagotribune O
: O
Update O
: O
FAA B-ORG
says O
no O
planes O
in O
U O
. O
S O
. O
destined O
to O
cross O
Midwest B-LOC
can O
depart O
until O
at O
least O
10 O
a O
. O
m O
. O
http://t.co/rArR4nDh9q O
h… O

RT O
@ESPNCFB O
: O
46 O
Days O
to O
Kickoff O
: O
Ohio B-ORG
State I-ORG
had O
46 O
plays O
that O
gained O
30 O
+ O
yds O
, O
2nd O
most O
in O
FBS B-OTHER
. O
#CountdownToKickoff O
http://t.co/zYvFgwgcAu O

. O
@MissAmerica O
2014 O
Nina B-PER
Davuluri I-PER
working O
with O
@TonyBowls O
at O
@MAOTeen O
in O
Orlando B-LOC
. O
#MissALovesTony O
http://t.co/sS9Dg750ml O

Got O
this O
huge O
Orchid O
at O
Aldi B-LOC
for O
Jill B-PER
. O
#orchid O
#Aldi B-ORG
http://t.co/GqYstZhX O

RT O
@ClassicPixs O
: O
Marilyn B-PER
Monroe I-PER
, O
1956 O
. O
Photograph O
by O
Milton B-PER
Greene I-PER
. O
. O
http://t.co/UO59nTNmN0 O

RT O
@HistoryInPics O
: O
Young O
women O
in O
Kabul B-LOC
, O
Afghanistan B-LOC
, O
1972 O
http://t.co/JjwXhAL8SZ O

RT O
@debra O
_ O
cothern O
: O
Beach O
glows O
like O
millions O
of O
stars O
at O
night O
- O
Maldives B-PER
http://t.co/3AKjfwXehX O

#tbt O
to O
the O
original O
1998 O
Off B-LOC
Broadway B-LOC
production O
of O
" O
Violet O
" O
- O
the O
latest O
Off B-LOC
Broadway B-LOC
musical O
to O
bow O
on O
Broadway B-LOC
. O
http://t.co/j4nWUsxVla O

RT O
@BrilliantPosts O
: O
Natural O
Swimming O
Pool O
in O
Thassos B-LOC
, O
Greece B-LOC
http://t.co/Uok1HhSA5B O

Nike B-ORG
Is O
Crushing O
It O
and O
on O
the O
Attack O
http://t.co/f7tCwaxWuG O
http://t.co/caE107ad5Z O

RT O
@NZStuff O
: O
Hurricanes B-ORG
honour O
Jerry B-PER
Collins I-PER
with O
big O
56-20 O
win O
over O
Highlanders B-ORG
in O
Napier B-LOC
http://t.co/KHbxWKlxWf O
http://t.co/tsrQ6Ty4oh O

RT O
@oldpicsarchive O
: O
Angela B-PER
Davis I-PER
and O
Toni B-PER
Morrison I-PER
taking O
a O
walk O
. O
March O
28 O
, O
1974 O
http://t.co/lr7wY0zqaT O

RT O
@MUFCScoop O
: O
Xavi B-PER
: O
" O
Maybe O
one O
small O
regret O
is O
that O
I O
never O
got O
to O
play O
with O
Paul B-PER
Scholes I-PER
. O
" O
#MUFC B-ORG
http://t.co/DybpXAmuo5 O

RT O
@BuzzFeed O
: O
audience O
Kanye B-PER
is O
quickly O
becoming O
our O
fav O
Kanye B-PER
http://t.co/PLDMzPcbdY O

RT O
@Bipartisanism O
: O
Bill B-PER
Clinton I-PER
and O
Barack B-PER
Obama I-PER
are O
the O
only O
two O
presidents O
in O
50 O
years O
to O
reduce O
the O
deficit O
. O
#tcot O
http://t.co/UCHyTLje… O

RT O
@ThislsAmazing O
: O
Bombing O
of O
Romania B-LOC
in O
World B-OTHER
War I-OTHER
II I-OTHER
http://t.co/sRYPCkVPJt O

RT O
@MODSUN O
: O
hey O
I O
' O
m O
Mod B-PER
. O
I O
' O
m O
in O
Italy B-LOC
right O
now O
. O
http://t.co/U1wgxWxxef O

RT O
@whpresscorps O
: O
RT O
@Reddy O
: O
Beau B-PER
Biden I-PER
, O
the O
son O
of O
Joe B-PER
Biden I-PER
, O
has O
died O
. O
The O
@VP O
statement O
: O
http://t.co/dut6rJqxaH O

And O
the O
iconic O
view O
from O
Brooklyn B-LOC
, O
a O
rare O
with O
the O
bridge O
and O
without O
the O
new O
Gehry O
tower O
http://t.co/JkK63Jd7GX O
http://t.co/fNIdwuP5M1 O

Take O
selfie O
&amp O
; O
post O
using O
#Glasgow2015 O
to O
win O
pair O
tickets O
to O
@IPCSwimming O
World O
Champs O
! O
Today O
in O
Buchanan B-LOC
St I-LOC
, O
Glasgow B-LOC
http://t.co/jAEMT2hVCy O

RT O
@EarthBeauties O
: O
San B-LOC
Francisco I-LOC
, O
California B-LOC
http://t.co/YSwJmC8P2j O

RT O
@NDFootball O
: O
Smith B-PER
and O
Tranquill B-PER
hug O
it O
out O
after O
taking O
down O
#14 O
Stanford B-ORG
at O
home O
. O
http://t.co/2mZrK4xqwd O

RT O
@iJDBsbelieber O
: O
same O
miley O
#MTVHottest O
Justin B-PER
Bieber I-PER
http://t.co/2GvhYKBmZp O

RT O
@MichelleRose014 O
: O
Show O
your O
love O
and O
support O
to O
end O
homophobia O
in O
Russia B-LOC
#SochiProblems O
#signoflove O
@lushcampaigns O
http://t.co/PMIQ6MOpo4 O

RT O
@momandwife3 O
: O
Brandon B-PER
Carr I-PER
of O
the O
Dallas B-ORG
Cowboys I-ORG
speaking O
to O
the O
kids O
at O
the O
sports O
camp O
at O
@ElevateLC O
http://t.co/f2BC0WlufC O

A O
couple O
of O
snow O
showers O
have O
moved O
into O
the O
Hudson B-LOC
Valley I-LOC
and O
New B-LOC
Jersey I-LOC
. O
@PIX11News O
http://t.co/lTzLrUdx5q O

Plumbers O
for O
Rahm B-PER
Emanuel I-PER
at O
their O
Union B-LOC
Hall I-LOC
. O
Election O
results O
coming O
in O
now O
: O
http://t.co/auLyUWHYzf O
http://t.co/2YktXvEbTb O

RT O
@EarthPicturz O
: O
Kilauea B-LOC
, O
on O
the O
Big B-LOC
Island I-LOC
of I-LOC
Hawaii I-LOC
, O
sends O
streams O
of I-LOC
lava O
steaming O
into O
the O
Pacific O
Ocean O
http://t.co/dtFtWyFikg O

RT O
@pdacosta O
: O
The O
war O
in O
Syriaq B-LOC
: O
Islamist B-OTHER
militants O
try O
to O
redraw O
map O
of O
Middle B-LOC
East I-LOC
http://t.co/avydvY8JoT O
http://t.co/RsEgZdsdU7 O

RT O
@dailykos O
: O
A O
lie O
in O
the O
Darren B-PER
Wilson I-PER
defense O
in O
the O
shooting O
death O
of O
Mike B-PER
Brown I-PER
that O
just O
won O
' O
t O
go O
away O
http://t.co/FUIfNPpypH O
http://… O

#Capetown O
#Helderberg B-LOC
#Overberg B-LOC
#Winelands O
Does O
anyone O
know O
any O
similar O
venues O
to O
play O
#Musicbythelake O
#Lovecapetown O
http://t.co/il0gWjqPck O

RT O
@girlposts O
: O
I O
wish O
I O
was O
in O
New B-OTHER
York I-LOC
for O
New B-OTHER
Years I-OTHER
http://t.co/bgax7t2VP8 O

Can O
anyone O
beat O
the O
Strattonator B-PER
in O
Adult B-ORG
A I-ORG
? O
Clearly O
not O
tonight O
as O
Matt B-PER
and O
Jim B-PER
can O
attest O
. O
http://t.co/QF5CQLtOEa O

Marian B-PER
Pledger I-PER
, O
graduated O
from O
@CLEMetroSchools O
in O
1959 O
believes O
@GWCarverCLE O
will O
create O
" O
Dreams O
" O
for O
kids O
#CTTT B-ORG
http://t.co/S6Q5mUQjW3 O

RT O
@AthIetesDesire O
: O
Drake B-PER
is O
a O
genius O
http://t.co/kmV7s4g8vV O

This O
Halloween B-OTHER
, O
the O
scariest O
place O
may O
be O
an O
overnight O
shift O
at O
the O
Security B-LOC
Operations I-LOC
Center I-LOC
http://t.co/cJFF3U39cU O
http://t.co/AKjGQhyb75 O

RT O
@ABCFpll O
: O
Who O
locked O
Emily B-PER
and O
Spencer B-PER
in O
the O
stAbles B-LOC
? O
#PLL O
http://t.co/teP16Me362 O

RT O
@Claritas O
: O
Dream O
job O
? O
The O
hottest O
career O
in O
America B-LOC
is O
compliance O
officer O
http://t.co/8mSevn8LH4 O
http://t.co/JgdC0fM3pV O

I O
am O
Duke B-OTHER
and O
I O
am O
7 O
weeks O
old O
http://t.co/JM8uZcGiDp O

RT O
@BostonGlobe O
: O
A O
braille O
trail O
in O
Essex B-LOC
County I-LOC
opens O
the O
woods O
for O
blind O
hikers O
http://t.co/M0wnqAIuRe O
http://t.co/3IaPtU8bUR O

From O
the O
#Ghana B-OTHER
Newsroom I-OTHER
: O
More O
than O
9 O
, O
000 O
Mormons O
in O
Ghana B-OTHER
Give I-OTHER
Community I-OTHER
Service I-OTHER
http://t.co/TQwudxDd02 O
#Mormon B-ORG
http://t.co/OJ15HbdbKO O

RT O
@MakingOfs O
: O
Harold B-PER
Ramis I-PER
on O
set O
with O
Annie B-PER
Potts I-PER
while O
filming O
" O
Ghostbusters B-OTHER
" O
, O
circa O
1983 O
http://t.co/YT2YkA3YDk O

RT O
@BuzzFeed O
: O
People O
in O
San B-LOC
Francisco I-LOC
waited O
in O
this O
crazy O
line O
for O
day-old O
NYC B-LOC
bagels O
http://t.co/596HVln7aR O
http://t.co/MGuD4cvtD0 O

RT O
@Gabriele O
_ O
Corno O
: O
Pink O
Umbrela O
@ O
St O
. O
Petersberg O
by O
Eduard B-PER
Gordeev I-PER
#Russia B-LOC
#CGE B-OTHER
#rain O
http://t.co/iXX7RdAbJt O

Poster O
near O
Kings B-LOC
Cross I-LOC
, O
London B-LOC
. O
http://t.co/7jRiFYanig O

RT O
@JustinKing224 O
: O
Hey O
kid O
, O
how O
many O
times O
has O
South B-LOC
Carolina I-LOC
beaten O
Clemson B-ORG
in O
a O
row O
? O
http://t.co/xd7pkSxpIC O

RT O
@UniversalHorror O
: O
Nana B-PER
' O
s O
been O
waiting O
. O
#TheVisitMovie O
opens O
in O
one O
month O
. O
http://t.co/Zr0vAyC9jv O

RT O
@SoccerrProblems O
: O
Messi B-PER
stays O
winning O
http://t.co/1iFyqjTMVl O

RT O
@Everytown O
: O
As O
of O
2013 O
, O
there O
are O
1 O
, O
141 O
licensed O
gun O
dealers O
in O
Louisiana B-LOC
, O
2 O
. O
3 O
times O
the O
number O
of O
post O
offices O
http://t.co/e4r2A8mRDa O

By O
the O
Charles B-LOC
River I-LOC
, O
still O
frozen O
. O
Spring O
is O
coming O
! O
http://t.co/SYZzBOVnqM O

Santorini B-LOC
, O
Grecia B-LOC
. O
RT O
@NaturPictures O
#luxury O
#Santorini B-LOC
#Greece B-LOC
#islands O
http://t.co/gzx5z2QSS7 O

RT O
@fubiz O
: O
Landscapes O
Timelapse B-OTHER
in O
Iceland B-LOC
and O
Greenland B-LOC
http://t.co/3GMKh8IrgP O
http://t.co/8bjq88pMEX O

Campaign O
trail O
for O
#ILGov O
w/ O
Rauner B-PER
http://t.co/uwXM576L9v O
and O
Quinn B-PER
http://t.co/LQYCOfaroz O
#photojournalism O
#twill O
http://t.co/sOrkGPIo81 O

RT O
@BEAUTIFULPlCS O
: O
Happy O
New B-OTHER
Year I-OTHER
from O
Washington B-LOC
D O
. O
C O
. O
! O
#NYE B-OTHER
#2015 O
http://t.co/41dPCKlcha O

RT O
@365QsFor1D O
: O
Louis B-PER
stop O
, O
please O
http://t.co/stPR24YVul O

NOW O
: O
Bethel B-ORG
AME I-ORG
in O
Jamaica B-LOC
Plain I-LOC
service O
for O
sister O
AME I-ORG
church O
in O
South B-LOC
Carolina I-LOC
. O
#fox25 O
http://t.co/l5JGHe1uEG O

Thank O
you O
to O
@LongwoodDental O
for O
their O
generous O
Thanksgiving B-OTHER
donation O
to O
Catholic B-LOC
Charities I-LOC
Laboure I-LOC
Center I-LOC
! O
http://t.co/pOJ8InbaPe O

Special O
delivery O
! O
! O
! O
From O
Portugal B-LOC
to O
North B-LOC
Wales I-LOC
: O
- O
) O
http://t.co/nOwz9OHPR5 O

We O
are O
now O
seeing O
shoes O
of O
civilian/police O
at O
Odin B-PER
Lloyd B-PER
crime O
scene O
after O
Lloyd B-PER
murder O
as O
Prosecution O
excludes O
them O
http://t.co/YdcT6Vbczj O

RT O
@ltsChuckBass O
: O
Chuck B-PER
Bass I-PER
is O
everything O
#MCM B-OTHER
http://t.co/gShCgU3U9b O

RT O
@Spotting1D O
: O
Harry B-PER
liked O
this O
picture O
on O
IG B-OTHER
! O
http://t.co/1mgr9xQ5Ha O

The O
@NU O
_ O
Sports O
women O
' O
s O
basketball O
team O
celebrates O
their O
first O
NCAA B-OTHER
bid O
since O
1997 O
. O
They O
head O
to O
Waco B-LOC
with O
a O
#7 O
seed O
http://t.co/SfgNKOwFMN O

Horrifying O
picture O
apparently O
showing O
the O
exact O
moment O
of O
explosion O
at O
the O
Boston B-OTHER
Marathon I-OTHER
https O
: O
//t O
. O
co/arj7yeXZhK O

Tomorrow O
marks O
the O
Wonderful O
236th O
Birthday O
of O
the O
United B-ORG
States I-ORG
Army I-ORG
- O
HOOAH O
! O
God O
Bless O
America B-LOC
! O
http://t.co/XiCLwpxC O
http://t.co/lnJBIBT4 O

This O
beautiful O
RL O
bag O
is O
in O
Macau B-LOC
, O
China B-LOC
. O
http://t.co/nYCZYyeU5F O

RT O
@jonathanchait O
: O
There O
' O
s O
a O
weird O
new O
meme O
that O
Clinton B-PER
' O
s O
campaign O
strategy O
is O
tearing O
America B-LOC
apart O
. O
http://t.co/Snc7HpyhIo O
http://t.co/F… O

RT O
@damonandelena11 O
: O
Elena B-PER
Gilbert I-PER
is O
finally O
WHOLE O
again O
*cries O
in O
beautiful* O
http://t.co/oh1B9F1ivK O

RT O
@antclausen O
: O
Liverpool B-LOC
Skyline O
this O
afternoon O
#liverpool B-LOC
#skyline O
#photography O
#blahblahblah O
http://t.co/x1HeDIerSl O

RT O
@PatsReport365 O
: O
Patriots B-ORG
owner O
Robert B-PER
Kraft I-PER
#20 O
when O
he O
played O
football O
http://t.co/8onsxtdJqJ O

RT O
@SportsCenter O
: O
Kings O
of O
New B-LOC
York I-LOC
. O
Rangers B-ORG
clinch O
Presidents O
' O
Trophy I-OTHER
with O
4-2 O
win O
over O
Devils B-ORG
. O
http://t.co/q3T5iLJdVF O

RT O
@AHedengren O
: O
#Aleppo B-LOC
before O
and O
after O
. O
#Syria B-LOC
. O
http://t.co/lFBstYoiVF O

RT O
@wgdunlop O
: O
Iraq B-LOC
tourism O
ministry O
statement O
saying O
it O
has O
eased O
entry O
procedures O
for O
tourist O
groups O
. O
http://t.co/elK2xwfh27 O

RT O
@Cap O
_ O
Institute O
: O
ALERT O
: O
Obama B-PER
Is O
Helping O
Hide O
These O
Rapists O
From O
America… O
They O
Could O
Be O
Next O
Door O
http://t.co/dsbg0szKsO O
#tcot O
http://t.c… O

RT O
@zodman100 O
: O
Why O
Shaqiri B-PER
rejected O
#LFC B-ORG
&amp O
; O
chosen O
to O
go O
to O
Stoke B-ORG
City I-ORG
. O
. O
. O
http://t.co/GEO9fjS8M4 O

RT O
@zellieimani O
: O
#SandraBland O
mural O
in O
Ottawa B-LOC
vandalized O
with O
the O
words O
in O
less O
than O
24 O
hours O
" O
#AllLivesMatter O
" O
http://t.co/2EGggKecSi O

RT O
@ManUtd O
: O
Retweet O
for O
@WayneRooney O
to O
win O
man O
of O
the O
match O
against O
Sunderland B-ORG
. O
#mufc B-ORG
http://t.co/0zJEeCrauF O

Campaign O
against O
xenophobia O
in O
London B-LOC
bus O
stops O
: O
http://t.co/h9GhCoZMWZ O
http://t.co/yPnjaoFxMG O

RT O
@RollingStone O
: O
Watch O
Bill B-PER
Murray I-PER
jump O
out O
of O
a O
cake O
for O
Letterman B-PER
on O
#LateShow O
: O
http://t.co/trdpiQNGhr O
http://t.co/MKcsT2mLtO O

Flying B-OTHER
Dutschman I-OTHER
by O
Richard B-PER
Wagner I-PER
at O
the O
ancient O
Roman B-LOC
theatre O
of O
Athens B-LOC
http://t.co/xbY3qpLPYS O

AMBER B-OTHER
ALERT I-OTHER
: O
Miya B-PER
Siverly I-PER
taken O
near O
Snowflake O
in O
dark O
green O
2000 B-OTHER
BUICK I-OTHER
LLF I-OTHER
, O
AZ B-LOC
plate O
BLA4754 O
. O
Call O
PD O
928-524-4050 O
http://t.co/E4iOAKrrW5 O

RT O
@ZacEfron O
: O
To O
my O
best O
girl- O
happy O
birthday O
angel O
. O
Love O
you O
Ash B-PER
. O
http://t.co/PEqCp2s0Fj O

RT O
@BakeOrama O
: O
Hope O
you O
and O
your O
mums O
All O
enjoyed O
the O
cakes O
and O
treats O
from O
myself O
and O
Wally B-PER
today O
! O
http://t.co/nFUIw71U7e O

One O
last O
round O
before O
we O
leave O
#Texas B-LOC
#christmas2013 O
http://t.co/t5lHplLsQB O

RT O
@taylorcaniff O
: O
Taylor B-PER
is O
on O
his O
meds O
xD O
He O
is O
going O
into O
surgery O
. O
Loves O
you O
guys O
! O
http://t.co/rmSo86qc1V O

How O
do O
we O
feel O
about O
Alabama B-LOC
using O
the O
Freedom B-OTHER
March I-OTHER
as O
a O
tourist O
draw O
? O
Serious O
question O
. O
http://t.co/6HZkLEQakG O

RT O
@daisyjuggalot O
: O
Ppl O
be O
like O
in O
Africa B-LOC
everyone O
have O
their O
hutts O
or O
live O
in O
the O
bush O
! O
Well O
Welcome O
to O
my O
#Hutt O
http://t.co/f6RQP3J24C O

RT O
@WTOP O
: O
Federal O
, O
Indiana B-LOC
authorities O
raid O
home O
of O
Subway O
spokesman O
Jared B-PER
Fogle I-PER
http://t.co/QB57yFvWOq O
http://t.co/ZRkSG9lfrM O

RT O
@L0gg0l O
: O
U O
. O
S O
deploys O
pair O
of O
B2 B-OTHER
stealth O
bombers O
to O
the O
UK B-LOC
to O
take O
part O
in O
NATO B-ORG
exercises O
http://t.co/dteifIiU3N O
http://t.co/AQDhlPLCsf O

RT O
@SouthernScenery O
: O
Outer B-LOC
Banks I-LOC
, O
North B-LOC
Carolina I-LOC
http://t.co/VgvTeyNnWz O

Kaisa B-LOC
Library I-LOC
in O
Helsinki B-LOC
. O
1 O
. O
5 O
million O
visitors O
every O
year O
. O
Beautiful O
piece O
of O
art O
and O
culture O
. O
Perfect O
atmosphere O
. O
http://t.co/wiLnIfLXTU O

RT O
@larlar1971 O
: O
Love O
by O
the O
Moon O
Waxing O
Crescent O
, O
Canon B-OTHER
600D I-OTHER
, O
Worcestershire B-LOC
, O
UK B-LOC
http://t.co/fr1TG9wqdA O

RT O
@BuzzFeed O
: O
Everything O
Lauren B-PER
Conrad I-PER
wore O
on O
the O
first O
season O
of O
" O
Laguna B-OTHER
Beach I-OTHER
" O
http://t.co/1TCVaWm2zG O
http://t.co/tepzhg0BiS O

RT O
@chelseafc O
: O
Our O
last O
10 O
league O
games O
away O
at O
Stoke B-ORG
City I-ORG
. O
. O
. O
http://t.co/RdsxE7efDz O
#CFC B-ORG
http://t.co/TkwmMAqHbM O

RT O
@maijapalmer O
: O
The O
best O
take O
so O
far O
on O
today O
; O
s O
Amazon B-ORG
story O
RT O
@QuantumPirate O
: O
I O
missed O
an O
Amazon B-ORG
drone O
delivery O
. O
http://t.co/dYFZWjR4GK O

RT O
@Amazing O
_ O
Maps O
: O
Alaska B-LOC
compared O
to O
Pluto B-LOC
http://t.co/bTracoT8pv O

Storage O
Requirements O
for O
Your O
Data B-OTHER
Lake I-OTHER
http://t.co/w67TtP3q7b O
http://t.co/O2yS1CTIhc O

Noticed O
for O
first O
time O
today O
( O
on O
big O
screen O
) O
that O
Spencer B-PER
Tracy I-PER
is O
in O
EVERY O
scene O
of I-OTHER
FATHER B-OTHER
OF I-OTHER
THE I-OTHER
BRIDE I-OTHER
. O
tcmff O
http://t.co/bUDN8FYwgM O

Last O
night O
at O
Cali B-LOC
, O
Colombia B-LOC
http://t.co/m9rOu3sOvQ O

RT O
@Newsweek O
: O
Obama B-PER
quest O
for O
fast-track O
#TPP B-OTHER
bill O
defeated O
in O
House O
for O
now O
http://t.co/opkvdCRJkf O
http://t.co/HzomfhrdR6 O

Black B-LOC
Sea I-LOC
fisherman O
. O
#Sochi B-LOC
Photos O
: O
http://t.co/7nO2tw28Om O
http://t.co/3VrsPUq1Go O

On O
this O
day O
in O
1890 O
, O
Wyoming B-LOC
became O
the O
44th O
state O
, O
allowing O
it O
to O
collaborate O
with O
other O
states O
on O
@Quip O
( O
at O
last O
) O
http://t.co/2vbdBjqczg O

Sailing O
Boat O
on O
the B-LOC
River B-LOC
Waveney I-LOC
in O
The B-LOC
Broads I-LOC
National I-LOC
Park I-LOC
. O
See O
more O
: O
http://t.co/p9aEL0pgoT O
http://t.co/rubvuIFBhg O

Mini B-OTHER
Cooper I-OTHER
Batman B-OTHER
edition O
. O
#wrooom O
#CapeTown O
http://t.co/F5V9B320s9 O

Practice O
for O
the O
Easter B-OTHER
play O
. O
#Easter B-OTHER
#Hunter O
#family O
#preschool O
#school O
#play O
http://t.co/ZBk1BbOmAL O

RT O
@CoachellaFSHN O
: O
Lana B-PER
Del I-PER
Rey I-PER
http://t.co/kNbzEQzGa8 O

RT O
@beautifulpixx O
: O
Zhangye B-LOC
Danxia I-LOC
Landform I-LOC
, O
Gansu B-LOC
, O
China B-LOC
http://t.co/XfjrkyzvoA O

RT O
@astro O
_ O
kjell O
: O
Hurricane O
#Jimena B-OTHER
lurking O
in O
the O
Pacific B-LOC
. O
http://t.co/TMOSFn8vGR O

RT O
@History O
_ O
Pics O
: O
Robert B-PER
DeNiro I-PER
and O
Al B-PER
Pacino I-PER
on O
the O
set O
of O
Godfather B-OTHER
II I-OTHER
, O
1974 O
. O
http://t.co/YqrAAtPC9M O

Matt B-PER
and O
his O
wife O
. O
Wth O
lol O
nvm O
its O
halloween B-OTHER
http://t.co/om4D6r44et O

Meet O
Lisa B-PER
Nichols I-PER
tomorrow O
at O
the O
next O
@ewomennetwork O
NYC B-LOC
event O
! O
https O
: O
//t O
. O
co/GWovTFggbP O
http://t.co/gTI4m0V5C1 O

RT O
@thehill O
: O
CBC B-ORG
chairman O
says O
race O
" O
a O
major O
factor O
in O
the O
delay O
" O
over O
Loretta B-PER
Lynch I-PER
vote O
: O
http://t.co/ZsGU0ItySk O
http://t.co/EWXexybEIz O

David B-PER
Denholm I-PER
from O
Kellogg B-ORG
kicking O
off O
the O
#ShareUrBreakfast O
DC B-LOC
event O
. O
RT O
to O
donate O
school O
bfast O
to O
kids O
in O
need O
! O
( O
cl O
) O
http://t.co/L6k7u6UW O

@noOrdinaryLove4 O
Hey O
Andrea B-PER
Check O
out O
this O
Event O
for O
the O
Marines B-ORG
! O
http://t.co/4QwkUaHTw7 O

Union B-ORG
Pacific I-ORG
train O
trestle O
in O
Gilbert B-LOC
goes O
up O
in O
flames O
. O
http://t.co/xT8HFxwufE O
http://t.co/qCaPVeDDoZ O

FUCK O
OPEC B-ORG
! O
Iran B-LOC
says O
an O
OPEC B-ORG
emergency O
meeting O
may O
stop O
oil O
price O
slide O
- O
Shana B-PER
http://t.co/zkuWQ5OcSW O
http://t.co/pVlaGVShEb O

RT O
@90swomen O
: O
Naomi B-PER
Campbell I-PER
and O
Michael B-PER
Jackson I-PER
x O
90s O
. O
http://t.co/O3gQ6B1sas O

RT O
@Cmdr O
_ O
Hadfield O
: O
Mexico B-LOC
City I-LOC
, O
one O
of O
the O
largest O
metropolitan O
areas O
on O
Earth O
- O
housing O
roughly O
the O
same O
population O
as O
Australia B-LOC
. O
http: O
... O

RT O
@KvanOosterom O
: O
Netherlands B-ORG
Navy I-ORG
counters O
piracy O
off O
coast O
Somalia B-LOC
, O
with O
frigate O
Johan B-OTHER
de I-OTHER
Witt I-OTHER
, O
here O
docking O
in O
#Seychelles B-LOC
http://t.co/j… O

RT O
@timelessbae O
: O
Eminem B-PER
&amp O
; O
Hailie B-PER
http://t.co/Z2hDd4sMYJ O

RT O
@rydercupEUROPE O
: O
Match O
3 O
. O
Rory B-PER
vs O
Rickie B-PER
. O
Retweet O
if O
you O
think O
Rory B-PER
wins O
. O
#GoEurope O
http://t.co/GQqgaF6krC O

Straight O
down O
from O
the O
103rd O
floor O
at O
Willis B-LOC
Tower I-LOC
today O
: O
http://t.co/XtdWmlTWYT O
http://t.co/kkRdzhnyYP O

He O
laid O
down O
His O
life O
for O
us O
, O
and O
we O
ought O
to O
lay O
down O
our O
lives O
for O
our O
brothers O
. O
1 O
John B-PER
3 O
: O
16 O
#WarriorBreakfast O
http://t.co/MpLj5lrkHx O

RT O
@ndtv O
: O
National B-ORG
Green I-ORG
Tribunal I-ORG
bans O
diesel O
vehicles O
older O
than O
10 O
years O
in O
Delhi B-LOC
http://t.co/6awdXdu5xp O
http://t.co/VZBl09ZdK4 O

Yes O
RT O
@ESPN O
_ O
FirstTake O
: O
Both B-PER
Skip I-PER
and O
Stephen B-PER
A O
. O
are O
going O
with O
FSU B-ORG
to O
beat O
Ga B-ORG
Tech I-ORG
. O
Do O
you O
agree O
? O
#CFBPicks O
http://t.co/4fTcHCigt5 O

RT O
@Skf3rn O
: O
Had O
an O
awesome O
time O
at O
#SDCC B-OTHER
and O
finally O
got O
to O
meet O
this O
gorgeous O
girl O
@Milloux O
#milloux B-PER
#SuicideGirls O
http://t.co/SyAnA72a8E O

Instagram B-ORG
bags O
seen O
at O
the O
Penang B-LOC
Camera I-LOC
Museum I-LOC
. O
#MyFest2015 O
#MalaysiaTrulyAsia O
#Penang B-LOC
#Malaysia B-LOC
#ttot O
http://t.co/G2Hsz6T46O O

RT O
@rabbleca O
: O
Harper B-PER
plans O
to O
privatize O
First B-OTHER
Nations I-OTHER
water O
services O
. O
WHY O
? O
http://t.co/J96wkLNJh2 O
#cdnpoli O
http://t.co/rZ0Rea6ZVs O

Attenborough B-PER
and O
Ben B-PER
Kingsley I-PER
with O
their O
Oscars B-OTHER
for O
Gandhi B-PER
. O
http://t.co/Lf8dqbs3rj O

RT O
@DazedMagazine O
: O
Watch O
a O
German B-LOC
news O
anchor O
call O
out O
racism O
against O
refugees O
live O
on O
air O
: O
http://t.co/uSktvWFTrq O
http://t.co/OnTKnlDec9 O

3 O
of O
the O
best O
places O
to O
eat O
lobster O
in O
the O
Caribbean B-LOC
http://t.co/Up3eobikhx O
http://t.co/bfjTQ6bggN O

Piedmont B-ORG
Together I-ORG
conference O
, O
GSO B-ORG
. O
Addressing O
ideas O
of O
growth O
strategies O
, O
walkability O
, O
food O
insecurity O
&amp O
; O
regionalism O
. O
http://t.co/mupCugLc0Q O

RT O
@Swiftwriting O
: O
Taylor B-PER
looking O
absolutely O
flawless O
at O
the O
BBC B-OTHER
Teen I-OTHER
Awards I-OTHER
. O
http://t.co/wKZkRO5Hz2 O

OUTSTANDING O
EMPLOYEE O
! O
Erin B-PER
at O
@MACcosmetics O
in O
Edina B-LOC
. O
So O
friendly O
&amp O
; O
no O
awkwardness O
for O
a O
TV O
man O
buying O
makeup O
! O
http://t.co/bx4SD3QuuQ O

RT O
@myfox8 O
: O
Charlotte B-PER
@hornets O
visit O
#Greensboro B-LOC
for O
D-League B-ORG
meeting O
http://t.co/wPed2zp1yA O
http://t.co/XUgMNab2xY O

RT O
@whiteboysdamn O
: O
Austin B-PER
Butler I-PER
appreciation O
tweet B-ORG
http://t.co/fPszbzBXwl O

RT O
@Mamba O
_ O
Insider O
: O
Every O
Kobe B-PER
Bryant I-PER
game O
winner O
🏀💯 O
http://t.co/R8SsGETR1f O

RT O
@TribGeoff O
: O
On O
its O
last O
day O
, O
Hot B-LOC
Doug I-LOC
' O
s O
closes O
line O
just O
after O
7 O
: O
30 O
http://t.co/VWpzEaCQZA O
http://t.co/z8PBz7ITod O

Kentucky B-LOC
law O
still O
recognizes O
Confederate B-OTHER
Memorial I-OTHER
Day/Jefferson O
Davis I-OTHER
Day I-OTHER
( O
June O
3 O
) O
and O
Robert B-OTHER
E O
. O
Lee I-OTHER
Day I-OTHER
( O
Jan O
. O
19 O
) O
. O
http://t.co/Gfg8w9vOa6 O

RT O
@Grapeapplesauce O
: O
Graser B-PER
using O
non O
Apple B-ORG
technology O
http://t.co/CGJid4rbGc O

@Jeckess5 O
Hey O
Jill B-PER
how O
are O
you O
! O
Please O
check O
out O
this O
Show O
in O
Vegas B-LOC
. O
http://t.co/giVDJta3yB O

Some O
businesses O
have O
been O
hit O
by O
the O
cold O
weather O
at O
night O
, O
but O
Karak B-LOC
outlets O
are O
doing O
well O
. O
http://t.co/nLDbWVYrux O
http://t.co/UPm3QsEi9X O

RT O
@myfox8 O
: O
Incredible O
photo O
of O
the O
tractor-trailer O
fire O
that O
has O
closed O
US B-LOC
52 O
near O
Rural B-LOC
Hall I-LOC
http://t.co/rISdq6gdmH O
http://t.co/QzBuL2tTND O

Great O
#travelpics O
post O
from O
the O
Summer B-OTHER
Solstice I-OTHER
fest I-OTHER
in O
#Poznan B-LOC
, O
Poland B-LOC
by O
@MartaTravelling O
http://t.co/U4V0clKb2X O
http://t.co/oVaIAEZYqT O

RT O
@chicagobulls O
: O
Bulls B-ORG
come O
back O
to O
win O
in O
dramatic O
fashion O
, O
98-97 O
over O
the O
Magic B-ORG
! O
http://t.co/AHE6l2ACQ3 O

Using O
External O
Resources O
when O
building O
#SAPLumira O
Viz O
Extensions O
in O
SAP B-OTHER
Web I-OTHER
IDE I-OTHER
: O
http://t.co/jw2ZCGr8nZ O
http://t.co/f6IBAbxLEV O

Paul O
is O
dead O
. O
RT O
@NobleF1 O
: O
Macau B-LOC
tries O
to O
recreate O
Abbey B-LOC
Road I-LOC
. O
. O
. O
Where O
is O
McCartney B-PER
? O
http://t.co/iORMFw7WBd O

I O
am O
Sasha B-OTHER
and O
I O
love O
to O
sleep O
http://t.co/JMBAdmwSWU O

RT O
@ChrisMegerian O
: O
Statement O
from O
Brown B-PER
spokesman O
on O
opposition O
to O
current O
version O
of O
SB B-OTHER
32 I-OTHER
http://t.co/X0F9Gmlb8L O

Erin B-PER
catches O
up O
on O
the O
news O
while O
waiting O
for O
her O
morning O
coffee O
. O
#WeReadHere O
#InternationalLiteracyDay O
http://t.co/mopYY8LzTD O

RT O
@JohnFarra O
: O
Wind O
storm O
damage O
causes O
canceled O
race O
in O
Sochi B-LOC
. O
Good O
luck O
to O
Georgy B-PER
&amp O
; O
OC O
to O
save O
the O
XC O
Sprint O
for O
tomorrow O
. O
http:// O
... O

RT O
@SouthernScenery O
: O
Charleston B-LOC
, O
South B-LOC
Carolina I-LOC
http://t.co/XIWWQ0Xata O

Hello O
, O
Israel B-LOC
! O
Tel B-LOC
Aviv I-LOC
and O
the O
view O
to O
Jaffa B-LOC
http://t.co/3igxdtEtuH O

RT O
@france7776 O
: O
Yezidi B-LOC
girls O
in O
#Sinjar O
defending O
themselves O
against O
ISIS B-ORG
rapists O
. O
v O
@KekHamo O
#Shingal O
http://t.co/K0e6tCzC95 O

Win O
tix O
to O
see O
LIGHTS B-OTHER
in O
Cleveland B-LOC
! O
Call O
me O
now O
at O
( O
330 O
) O
672-7700 O
&amp O
; O
tell O
me O
Lights B-OTHER
' O
daughter O
' O
s O
name O
&amp O
; O
they O
' O
re O
yours O
! O
http://t.co/iOGZTyJfWi O

RT O
@AmazingRoom O
: O
Breathtaking O
Cherry O
Blossoms O
in O
Japan B-LOC
http://t.co/F2HFQ8g13D O

RT O
@onedirection O
: O
Dublin B-LOC
, O
Croke O
Park O
. O
. O
. O
Are O
you O
ready O
for O
this O
? O
#WWATour O
http://t.co/zI4SEccsl7 O

The O
day O
after O
, O
our O
family O
gathers O
in O
our O
spot O
on O
the O
Penobscot B-LOC
River I-LOC
, O
Maine B-LOC
http://t.co/g69ugwyFto O

I O
just O
read O
the O
article O
Balotelli B-PER
hungry O
for O
more O
after O
. O
. O
. O
using O
the O
Official O
UEFA B-ORG
EURO O
2012 O
app O
http://t.co/sjMZQBL7 O
http://t.co/di3tLiij O

RT O
@TrooperBenKHP O
: O
Good O
morning O
Kansas B-LOC
! O
http://t.co/soPH10KGU5 O

RT O
@90sfootball O
: O
Ronaldo B-PER
vs O
Pep B-PER
Guardiola I-PER
, O
1999 O
. O
http://t.co/X6BEd6cVRU O

RT O
@LowKei O
_ O
: O
When O
Bey B-PER
said O
" O
and O
thank O
you O
to O
my O
Bey B-PER
Hive O
" O
at O
the O
Grammys B-OTHER
. O
http://t.co/dXjRi41stj O

RT O
@Wally O
_ O
Mayz O
: O
VMA B-OTHER
producers O
watching O
Kanye B-PER
in O
the O
green O
room O
like O
http://t.co/4PHziOZ5ra O

I O
refuse O
to O
buy O
#Facebook B-ORG
likes O
and O
#Twitter B-ORG
followers O
and O
this O
is O
the O
reason O
why O
- O
http://t.co/jaKD2sGBP6 O
http://t.co/Yd63LoLnqK O

Shark B-LOC
Cove I-LOC
on O
Long B-LOC
Island I-LOC
, O
Maine B-LOC
http://t.co/6z6914ggHJ O

RT O
@ajcbraves O
: O
#Braves B-ORG
Gattis B-PER
http://t.co/YWeQkjxY O

RT O
@9NEWS O
: O
#BREAKING O
: O
Police O
release O
sketch O
of O
vehicle O
of O
interest O
in O
northern O
CO B-ORG
shootings O
. O
Tip O
line O
: O
970-498-5595 O
http://t.co/zxxkxqO8ul O

Incoming O
: O
Tulsa B-LOC
photog O
made O
a O
sweet O
wide-angle O
frame O
, O
then O
receiver O
broke O
his O
400 O
2 O
. O
8 O
in O
half O
http://t.co/kdAWRBMnMd O
http://t.co/pG3lej4JHA O

Trippy B-PER
Beatz I-PER
is O
the O
the O
old O
Sleazy B-PER
Beatz I-PER
account O
. O
Ugh O
, O
RIP O
Sleazy B-PER
Beatz I-PER
. O
You O
are O
missed O
#staySLEAZY O
http://t.co/pUxj3TrDJt O

RT O
@HitDaBoogieZ O
: O
Nigga B-PER
said O
I O
look O
like O
I O
bark O
at O
people O
. O
http://t.co/5QGcweao8Q O

Alex B-PER
Ovechkin I-PER
Interviewed O
by O
ABC B-ORG
Crew I-ORG
during O
the O
Lunch O
time O
at O
Mari B-LOC
Vanna I-LOC
DC I-LOC
! O
#marivannadc O
@ovi8 O
@ABC O
http://t.co/duIo6DJLyY O

RT O
@thewonderwheel O
: O
Bill B-PER
Murray I-PER
as O
Han B-PER
Solo I-PER
? O
Yes O
, O
please O
! O
#SDCC B-OTHER
http://t.co/gXUqcr0l0r O
http://t.co/jCRhHG5NuM O

#TBLighting O
Alex B-PER
Killorn I-PER
tips O
a O
puck O
around O
#Blackhawks B-ORG
Corey B-PER
Crawford I-PER
' O
s O
skate O
for O
a O
goal O
http://t.co/15beLF6Ajw O
http://t.co/zLcSXaaPnc O

Toews B-PER
&amp O
; O
Kane B-PER
#Blackhawks O
poster O
in O
Sunday O
' O
s O
@chicagotribune O
. O
Re-live O
the O
Stanley B-OTHER
Cup I-OTHER
moment O
: O
http://t.co/xhuAR9UjgB O
http://t.co/RLWMGNExgA O

@ROGAstronomers O
shot O
from O
Derby B-LOC
, O
UK B-LOC
( O
12th O
August O
) O
#perseid O
http://t.co/YDCOj6hHbq O

RT O
@SteveMariucci O
: O
Gettin O
ready O
for O
the O
Draft O
at O
Raos-- O
NYC B-LOC
! O
! O
http://t.co/BTY7sXRez4 O

A O
Policy O
Panel O
getting O
started O
w O
EPA B-ORG
, O
Wisconsin B-ORG
DNR I-ORG
, O
Fond O
du I-LOC
Lac I-LOC
Band I-LOC
, O
and O
@MnPCA O
#HgForum O
http://t.co/ohbbRX5CDE O

Good O
Morning O
Zaatari B-LOC
! O
#Syria B-LOC
http://t.co/LNyJK7Y5uc O

Hat O
tip O
to O
our O
customer O
@Walmart O
for O
its O
new O
#JUMP B-OTHER
effort O
in O
support O
of O
US B-LOC
#manufacturing O
http://t.co/9q4JIO4LD1 O
http://t.co/M75GeZbl2T O

RT O
@fitsnews O
: O
Jeb B-PER
Bush I-PER
Goes O
After O
Donald B-PER
Trump I-PER
- O
http://t.co/QpOK1us7Fx O
http://t.co/G7kN3oZ1to O

@JihadistJoe O
from O
the O
dorm O
of O
Islamist B-OTHER
students O
supporting O
Morsi B-PER
in O
egypt B-LOC
http://t.co/aYKMJQKJ7C O

Come O
meet O
KABIBE B-OTHER
on O
Saturday O
, O
December O
21 O
, O
starting O
at O
10 O
: O
00am O
! O
Photo O
by O
Marianne B-PER
Hale I-PER
http://t.co/W0IAWWTHpW O

RT O
@PaulHeggenWSMV O
: O
Tornado O
Warning O
for O
Wilson B-LOC
county O
. O
Rotation O
just O
south O
of O
Lebanon B-LOC
. O
http://t.co/t4S5CO8C3H O

Preparing O
the O
sand O
at O
Hayes B-LOC
Beach I-LOC
for O
Memorial B-OTHER
Day I-OTHER
weekend O
. O
Chicago B-LOC
beaches O
open O
Saturday O
! O
http://t.co/dc9yXUuPvf O

RT O
@bartongellman O
: O
NYC B-LOC
subway O
camera O
poster O
, O
edited O
for O
clarity O
. O
( O
2 O
train O
, O
today O
. O
) O
Never O
saw O
this O
before O
#Snowden B-PER
. O
http://t.co/geRckDZHQl O

RT O
@pl1949 O
: O
Welcome O
to O
St O
. O
Petersburg I-LOC
, O
Russia B-LOC
http://t.co/7l0w8SIWDV O
#Citybreaks O
#travel O
http://t.co/VPZeXKKKOi O

RT O
@McKinsey O
: O
Almost O
70 O
% O
of O
the O
mobile O
connections O
in O
India B-LOC
and O
China B-LOC
are O
on O
2G B-OTHER
networks O
http://t.co/TNYFSRrAO9 O
http://t.co/RmeW5lEGta O

http://t.co/IW82EF0ZFq O
Why O
rape O
"works" O
as O
oppression O
&amp; O
why O
the O
UN B-LOC
does O
not: O
interesting O
views O
from O
Madeleine... O
http://t.co/63Hf3IhT89 O

CPD B-ORG
officer O
injured O
after O
vehicle O
flips O
at O
Ashland/Montrose O
. O
Intersection O
closed O
, O
avoid O
http://t.co/Slgvs8y2Nc O

RT O
@rappersaid O
: O
When O
Megan B-PER
from O
Drake B-PER
and O
Josh B-PER
said O
, O
" O
well O
why O
was O
ur O
door O
under O
my O
bucket O
" O
http://t.co/bnRToQbgSa O

RT O
@FCBarcelona O
: O
From O
Zarra B-PER
to O
Messi B-PER
: O
The O
legend O
continues O
http://t.co/CRtSVsKs5g O
http://t.co/pLMSstF1Js O

RT O
@jessefelder O
: O
Ray B-PER
Dalio I-PER
on O
the O
markets O
, O
economy O
and O
Fed B-ORG
: O
http://t.co/4Cfy9urZMV O
http://t.co/QrQcrWWR2S O

JJ B-PER
Watt I-PER
RT O
@nflnetwork O
: O
Who O
should O
win O
MVP B-OTHER
this O
season O
? O
Coming O
up O
on O
#GameDayFirst O
. O
http://t.co/jq8PjUS08Y O

RT O
@Bipartisanism O
: O
This O
grandma O
has O
a O
message O
for O
Indiana B-LOC
lawmakers O
. O
#BoycottIndiana O
http://t.co/egNJLOH7FJ O

RT O
@90sfootball O
: O
Miguel B-PER
Angel I-PER
Nadal I-PER
poses O
with O
his O
nephew O
and O
future O
tennis O
star O
Rafael B-PER
Nadal I-PER
. O
http://t.co/9DYpcVwuAK O

RT O
@Samantha O
_ O
Brophy O
: O
" O
@EarthPicsx O
: O
Tulip B-OTHER
fields O
in O
Holland B-LOC
. O
http://t.co/wiQL55OmrJ" O
@janelleeevb O

RT O
@FearInSociety O
: O
Father O
of O
Miss O
Bakari B-PER
who O
was O
the O
victim O
of O
the O
#McKinney B-LOC
incident O
. O
Never O
stop O
RTing O
this O
http://t.co/7YZnZRVy6y O

RT O
@BBCOne O
: O
Dear O
Madonna B-PER
, O
THIS O
is O
how O
you O
wear O
a O
cape O
. O
#Poldark B-OTHER
#Demelza B-OTHER
http://t.co/k9zs5onDeI O

#FIFA2014 O
hair O
! O
This O
style O
was O
created O
by O
the O
Orenorkobi B-OTHER
Artistic I-OTHER
Team I-OTHER
, O
who O
are O
based O
in O
Tel B-LOC
Aviv I-LOC
, O
Israel B-LOC
#WellaHair O
http://t.co/5k6yznbSuK O

Lady B-PER
Gaga I-PER
on O
David B-OTHER
Letterman I-OTHER
tonight O
. O
http://t.co/ASc5BTkgIe O

V O
was O
for O
victory O
for O
the O
Caps B-ORG
today O
at O
Nats B-LOC
Park I-LOC
http://t.co/RKDF0AwXeQ O

With O
@stormfitnesspt O
in O
Newcastle B-LOC
curing O
Plantar B-OTHER
on O
#Stoptober B-ORG
. O
. O
. O
http://t.co/wCZQBh4Ilm O

A O
Sudbury B-LOC
couple O
killed O
in O
the O
USVI B-LOC
. O
. O
. O
their O
adopted O
son O
accused O
. O
. O
. O
Those O
that O
knew O
them O
at O
10 O
and O
11 O
#fox25 O
http://t.co/LqgzonXkCg O

RT O
@dreamteamfc O
: O
Still O
coming O
to O
terms O
with O
the O
fact O
that O
Charlie B-PER
Adam I-PER
and O
Ibrahim B-PER
Afellay I-PER
are O
both O
29 O
. O
http://t.co/j7HlJYt8NH O

RT O
@LSJNews O
: O
Pride O
flags O
at O
local O
GM B-ORG
plants O
supported O
equality O
, O
said O
official O
http://t.co/8vrbep8XKp O
http://t.co/EqStgTSddl O

Back O
on O
the O
commons O
for O
Col B-PER
and O
Matt B-PER
' O
s O
wedding O
@ScrantonAlumni O
#scranton O
http://t.co/CFiudwL0DJ O

Apple B-ORG
Tumbles O
to O
Samsung B-ORG
as O
Smartphone O
Shipment O
Leader O
http://t.co/IpNMl7dDK4 O
https://t.co/MF4Z16T0PX O
http://t.co/TENTIjHTPv O

A O
crazy O
beautiful O
East B-LOC
Coast I-LOC
day O
. O
. O
. O
#oldsturbridgevillage O
#Massachusetts B-LOC
http://t.co/ZOZFK1f6De O

Watchin O
Martin B-PER
when O
the O
beautiful O
@niccigilbert O
was O
on O
there O
. O
http://t.co/BFNC6pZVVz O

@sternshow O
: O
Whoopi B-PER
Goldberg I-PER
talking O
to O
#Howard B-OTHER
on O
stage O
http://t.co/iTcpNbm7rF O
wow!!! O

Is O
it O
raining O
? O
Some O
wet O
United B-LOC
Center I-LOC
seats O
before O
the O
#Blackhawks O
drop O
the O
puck O
http://t.co/xRJmjp0e1Q O

RT O
@b0ringtweets O
: O
Bantman B-OTHER
and O
Robin B-PER
. O
#sillysausages O
http://t.co/fIbt95xMxA O

You O
are O
invited O
to O
our O
BBQ B-OTHER
Garden I-OTHER
Party I-OTHER
on O
Sat O
20 O
September O
at O
deafPLUS B-LOC
, O
Trinity B-LOC
Centre I-LOC
, O
London B-LOC
. O
Pls O
RT O
and O
share O
. O
http://t.co/PPhPvQZLFv O

RT O
@sen O
: O
SpaceX B-ORG
reveals O
#DragonV2 B-OTHER
designed O
to O
transport O
astronauts O
to O
low O
Earth O
orbit O
http://t.co/sgGTsJRkNG O
http://t.co/XZ5Q479h2w O

BREAKING O
: O
IPC B-ORG
President O
Sir O
Philip B-PER
Craven I-PER
praises O
@Glasgow2014 O
as O
a O
" O
tremendous O
success O
" O
http://t.co/mOY3E03KPR O
http://t.co/Pyzgd5CyKe O

@Bflucky O
@EddieEddiboy70 O
Remy B-PER
wants O
you O
to O
lay O
back O
, O
relax O
and O
enjoy O
your O
Caturday O
! O
Especially O
, O
Daisy B-PER
! O
; O
) O
http://t.co/njN8RiKp61 O

RT O
@brouardbenoit01 O
: O
IBM B-ORG
is O
betting O
$ O
3 O
billion O
on O
the O
Internet B-OTHER
of I-OTHER
Things I-OTHER
, O
but O
will O
it O
pay O
off O
? O
http://t.co/CGRMyOSLNC O
http://t.co/T9Gh8wQXOp O

My O
coworker O
made O
cookies O
that O
look O
like O
Sulley B-OTHER
from O
Monsters B-ORG
Inc I-ORG
. O
http://t.co/yj7bkiNT8B O

RT O
@TheRoot O
: O
Byron B-PER
Allen I-PER
files O
$ O
20 O
billion O
discrimination O
lawsuit O
against O
Comcast B-ORG
and O
Al B-PER
Sharpton I-PER
http://t.co/hFbQNieywS O
http://t.co/05X87u… O

@HistoryInPics O
: O
Bill B-PER
Cosby I-PER
in O
a O
sea O
of O
Bill B-PER
Cosby I-PER
' O
s O
. O
1968 O
via O
LIFE O
. O
http://t.co/SjkIYWE5WV O
@CrustacheBrown O

New O
shop O
serves O
up O
Hong B-LOC
Kong I-LOC
waffles O
&amp O
; O
ice O
cream O
http://t.co/FSQwnijZ0q O
http://t.co/FLBfShT0i3 O
via O
@ O
blogto O

RT O
@KennettDems O
: O
RT O
if O
you O
did O
, O
too O
! O
#GOTV B-ORG
http://t.co/vbVf73wMlw O

Found O
this O
board O
game O
at O
the O
Chelsea B-OTHER
Flea I-OTHER
Market I-OTHER
. O
Oh O
how O
the O
times O
have O
changed O
for O
Bruce B-PER
. O
. O
. O
. O
http://t.co/UoY67xHH O

RT O
@clarissGn O
: O
Morning O
light O
, O
Budapest B-LOC
, O
1931 O
. O
By O
Imre B-PER
kinszki I-PER
. O
http://t.co/Kha0qsZVg1 O

Very O
useful O
meeting O
with O
Laura B-PER
Tuck I-PER
, O
#Vice-President O
for O
#Europe B-LOC
and O
#Central B-LOC
Asia I-LOC
of O
the O
#World B-ORG
Bank I-ORG
. O
http://t.co/9qPChFav3s O

#Blackhawks B-ORG
Andrew B-PER
Desjardins I-PER
with O
the O
first O
goal O
of O
the O
game O
against O
the O
#Predators B-ORG
. O
http://t.co/D2ztvVmqw8 O
http://t.co/l18KQ44h2y O

@NationalZoo O
#PandaCam2 O
Depressed O
by O
the O
shutdown O
, O
Lucy B-OTHER
the O
Panda O
started O
off O
her O
morning O
with O
a O
large O
glass O
of O
wine O
http://t.co/s9AoHnzyu3 O

RT O
@sibradley1 O
: O
Interns O
in O
Geneva B-LOC
join O
May O
1 O
protest O
over O
pay O
and O
work O
conditions O
. O
http://t.co/uJlu9OTnVW O

Need O
scale-out O
NAS B-ORG
to O
meet O
your O
data O
retention O
needs O
? O
Isilon B-ORG
can O
help O
: O
http://t.co/y0o3LP2F0T O
http://t.co/DkMkkPK5kV O

The O
City O
of O
Cape B-LOC
Town I-LOC
at O
night O
. O
. O
. O
Photo O
by O
Regardt B-PER
Stander I-PER
. O
#Travel O
#BeautifulPlaces O
http://t.co/T6QXEGkQ6I O

Swedish O
game O
Minecraft B-OTHER
bought O
by O
Microsoft B-ORG
- O
Mojang B-ORG
AB I-ORG
got O
2 O
, O
5 O
BUSD O
! O
" O
Notchs O
" O
is O
happy O
! O
@SwedeninHR O
http://t.co/h5Z337QzIZ O

Pritzker B-LOC
Pavilion I-LOC
and O
the O
Michigan B-LOC
Avenue I-LOC
street O
wall O
. O
Thanks O
, O
Frank B-PER
Gehry I-PER
! O
http://t.co/FUCngLIDqV O

RT O
@CIothesPorn O
: O
USA B-LOC
defender O
Julie B-PER
Johnston I-PER
is O
perfection O
http://t.co/2eFrDFoJtx O

RT O
@RembranceOfPast O
: O
Skateboarding O
in O
New B-LOC
York I-LOC
City I-LOC
, O
1965 O
http://t.co/hVcuVroMDI O

RT O
@GAFollowers O
: O
Georgia B-LOC
born O
NFL B-OTHER
player O
Eric B-PER
Berry I-PER
has O
successfully O
defeated O
cancer O
. O
http://t.co/XDPPM7HmKh O

RT O
@johnnydphoto O
: O
TP&amp O
; O
W B-PER
releases O
204 O
, O
000 O
largemouth O
bass O
into O
Medina B-LOC
Lake I-LOC
, O
http://t.co/jcKcIvEzmn, O
SA O
Express-News O
http://t.co/FxUbK4wx65 O

State O
Sen O
. O
Anitere B-PER
Flores I-PER
speaking O
to O
crowd O
. O
" O
If O
this O
country O
doesn O
' O
t O
demand O
freedom O
in O
Cuba B-LOC
, O
then O
who O
will O
? O
" O
http://t.co/wHsWNsU4yD O

RT O
@IsabelHardman O
: O
In O
reception O
at O
BBC B-ORG
in O
Salford B-LOC
Michael B-PER
Gove I-PER
appears O
to O
be O
manning O
the O
phones O
http://t.co/dIoIF81PSM O

This O
#AfghanProverb O
( O
#Pashto B-OTHER
) O
means O
that O
seeing O
your O
own O
faults O
is O
as O
hard O
as O
seeing O
your O
own O
back O
. O
@SpeakAfghan O
http://t.co/FBBP0TgdP6 O

RT O
@EnglishRussia1 O
: O
" O
We O
better O
stay O
home O
" O
. O
Vladivostok B-LOC
, O
Russia B-LOC
http://t.co/5DpfBGAGGQ O

RT O
@Know O
: O
Bruce B-PER
Lee I-PER
doing O
a O
one O
hand O
push-up O
, O
using O
only O
an O
index O
finger O
and O
a O
thumb O
. O
http://t.co/5nUeZ3DyPJ O

Niners B-ORG
staff O
pack O
it O
up O
, O
they O
' O
re O
moving O
back O
to O
Candlestick B-LOC
after O
#Bears B-ORG
ruin O
opening O
night O
at O
Field B-LOC
of I-LOC
Jeans I-LOC
http://t.co/SJLl7fqhRm O

RT O
@YourMCFC O
: O
Seven O
years O
ago O
today O
#MCFC B-ORG
were O
taken O
over O
by O
Sheikh B-PER
Mansour I-PER
. O
Manchester B-LOC
thanks O
you O
, O
Sheikh B-PER
Mansour I-PER
! O
http://t.co/OdIJikaImZ O

Pittsburgh B-LOC
5 O
minutes O
ago O
http://t.co/LKarxboTwh O

RT O
@SAVx O
: O
Kanye B-PER
: O
" O
KIM B-PER
GET O
OUT O
IM O
NOT O
READY O
YET O
" O
http://t.co/QnUoe6xbhn O

And O
this O
is O
proof O
that O
the O
US B-LOC
is O
behind O
in O
fashion O
, O
I O
bought O
this O
sweater O
in O
Europe B-LOC
last O
winter O
( O
except O
in O
grey O
) O
http://t.co/E5YU6zXWoP O

Holicray-cray O
! O
Use O
your O
Starbucks B-OTHER
Card I-OTHER
every O
day O
for O
a O
chance O
to O
win O
#StarbucksforLife O
http://t.co/ZwaG8G1IX5 O
http://t.co/fzsh9Jpce1 O

When O
in O
George B-LOC
Town I-LOC
, O
Try O
the O
Penang B-LOC
Road I-LOC
Famous O
Chendul B-OTHER
. O
#MyFest2015 O
#MalaysiaTrulyAsia O
#Penang B-LOC
#food O
#ttot O
http://t.co/tv6MrNvix4 O

Loki B-PER
is O
happy O
@primantibros O
ships O
to O
Baltimore B-LOC
now O
. O
He O
just O
wishes O
he O
could O
eat O
it O
. O
@goldbely O
#ShipThatMeat O
http://t.co/w8xcf97nzS O

RT O
@threatintel O
: O
#vulnerability O
: O
iCloud B-OTHER
#Apple B-OTHER
ID I-OTHER
Dictionary O
attack O
tool O
surfaces O
on O
GitHub B-ORG
http://t.co/u9LIaq33LG O
http://t.co/NBt1RtjUSY O

RT O
@MissUniversNEWS O
: O
Megan B-PER
Young I-PER
from O
Philippines B-LOC
, O
the O
next O
Miss B-OTHER
World I-OTHER
? O
https O
: O
//t O
. O
co/x8ssQtnphS O
http://t.co/1W7sFjLXoD O

RT O
@nbc6 O
: O
JUST O
IN O
: O
David B-PER
Carr I-PER
, O
New B-ORG
York I-ORG
Times I-ORG
Media O
Columnist O
, O
Dead O
at O
58 O
http://t.co/z5Nwf4TqQQ O
http://t.co/HuBkggyV3S O

Congrats O
to O
TWO O
#MariettaAward O
winners O
, O
Ashley B-PER
&amp O
; O
Christine B-PER
at O
PF B-LOC
Indianapolis I-LOC
, O
IN B-LOC
. O
Keep O
making O
members O
feel O
welcome O
! O
http://t.co/2Cuzg755yk O

SPAIN B-LOC
- O
A O
boy O
sits O
between O
" O
Cabezudos O
" O
at O
City B-LOC
Hall I-LOC
of I-LOC
Pamplona I-LOC
during O
the O
San B-OTHER
Fermin I-OTHER
Festival I-OTHER
. O
By O
@MiguelRiopa O
#AFP B-OTHER
http://t.co/S3GLg7x6Mz O

RT O
@Cum O
_ O
n O
_ O
mybooty O
: O
Lil B-PER
Kim I-PER
looks O
like O
someone O
from O
the O
Purge O
http://t.co/OpzYMf72kr O

RT O
@TheEconomist O
: O
The B-ORG
Economist I-ORG
explains O
why O
Africa B-LOC
is O
becoming O
less O
dependent O
on O
commodities O
http://t.co/RyGzMdqh6M O
http://t.co/xCfNpnDtcA O

RT O
@bestvocaIists O
: O
Zayn B-PER
Malik I-PER
is O
so O
talented O
. O
http://t.co/D0R1ejN7pa O

Happy O
Independence B-OTHER
day I-OTHER
, O
Finland B-LOC
! O
#proudtobeafinn O
http://t.co/NjO5GUBg O

Spruce O
up O
the O
yard O
and O
spread O
the O
word O
at O
the O
same O
time O
. O
@VoteLorena O
Get O
yours O
at O
590 B-LOC
Park I-LOC
Way I-LOC
in O
Chula B-LOC
Vista I-LOC
http://t.co/27XHgcJX3k O

RT O
@cppluxury O
: O
Bally B-ORG
opens O
flagship O
store O
in O
London B-LOC
http://t.co/JE4x6MtIgw O
#BallyMayfairWelcome O
#BallyLondon O
http://t.co/gLEpGNLYof O

Taha B-PER
and O
Alex B-PER
wedding O
http://t.co/Wyd0iySMLG O

RT O
@SOHPoralhistory O
: O
SOHP B-OTHER
Interim O
Director O
Della B-PER
Pollock I-PER
is O
featured O
on O
the O
UNC B-ORG
website O
! O
Check O
it O
out O
! O
http://t.co/2r0q2xMM O
http://t.co/ O
... O

RT O
@GREATBritain O
: O
The O
magnificent O
walls O
of O
Arundel B-LOC
castle O
can O
be O
found O
in O
West B-LOC
Sussex I-LOC
http://t.co/FKnoucH0Dv O
http://t.co/QdibaftW9b O

24 O
Questions O
Britain B-LOC
Has O
For O
Australia B-LOC
http://t.co/FslgiFx7X5 O
http://t.co/9JVQ707piY O

The O
@PredsFoundation O
made O
a O
special O
delivery O
to O
Barefoot B-LOC
Republic I-LOC
this O
week O
--&gt O
; O
http://t.co/TbYY3syU6N O
#Preds B-ORG
http://t.co/ttoGpFnLme O

@1bluecube O
Hey O
Tami B-PER
how O
are O
you O
! O
Please O
check O
out O
this O
show O
in O
Vegas B-LOC
http://t.co/QZFijaBEtY O

Postcard O
Chicago B-LOC
from O
Trib B-LOC
Tower I-LOC
. O
More O
views O
and O
@BlairKamin O
review O
of O
Mich B-LOC
Ave I-LOC
renovations O
: O
http://t.co/Oy00MfPRpf O
http://t.co/w3ff4FocXl O

NEW O
: O
Incredibly O
Quirky B-OTHER
Chalk I-OTHER
Art I-OTHER
Born O
in O
the O
Streets O
, O
by O
David B-PER
Zinn I-PER
http://t.co/Xd9Gw8f81Z O
- O
http://t.co/aueV8nwMfu O

Baikal O
, O
in O
Russia B-LOC
. O
. O
. O
http://t.co/RkEhaGXm0F O

RT O
@travelwith2ofus O
: O
@CaribbeJan O
@YourConcierge O
_ O
@FlySeaborne O
Nice O
. O
Love O
it O
. O
Sweet O
#Caribbean B-LOC
Many O
choices O
. O
#travel O
http://t.co/DQzaRPi0zq O

#TBLightning O
Garrison B-PER
throws O
#Blackhawks B-ORG
Shaw O
to O
the O
ice O
in O
the O
1st O
. O
Blog O
: O
http://t.co/15beLF6Ajw O
http://t.co/CYSfpmc181 O

RT O
@BuzzFeedNews O
: O
Zoo O
Animals O
In O
Georgia B-LOC
On O
The O
Loose O
After O
Devastating O
Floods O
http://t.co/XBmjvpHuFb O
http://t.co/0md4Kb2JyQ O

RT O
@mbindwane O
: O
Meanwhile O
in O
Australia B-LOC
. O
. O
. O
. O
http://t.co/Yi9Igi8mbL O

RT O
@YahooMusic O
: O
Prince O
is O
in O
the O
house O
to O
present O
Record O
of O
the O
Year O
to O
. O
. O
. O
. O
Gotye B-PER
! O
-Laura O
F I-PER
Grammys B-OTHER
. O
http://t.co/a6pgNLlS O

Maria B-PER
Ihekwaba I-PER
and O
supporters O
cheer O
as O
television O
networks O
show O
Rahm B-PER
Emanuel I-PER
with O
in O
lead O
http://t.co/auLyUWHYzf O
http://t.co/zFlrNYuWoC O
